她在那儿!
There she is!
格洛里亚!
Gloria!
嗨。
Hi.
欢迎光临!
Welcome!
-你看起来棒极了。-谢谢!
- You look great. - Thank you!
-达西，你去哪儿了?——嘿!这就跟你问声好！
- Darcy, where have you been? - Hey! Hi!
我只是花了一分钟。这样可以吗?
I was just taking a minute. Is that allowed?
不是在你的婚礼上。
Not at your wedding.
-你的凯特尔一号马提尼。——哦。
- Your Ketel One martini. - Oh.
Obrigada,杰罗姆。
Obrigada, Jerome.
新郎呢?
Where is the groomzilla?
汤姆不是伴郎，好吗?
Tom is not a groomzilla, okay?
他只是致力于让每个细节都完美。
He just committed to making every detail perfect.
这场婚礼你应该拿你父亲的钱。
You should have taken your father's money for this wedding.
然后，专业人士会为你做好一切。
Then, professionals would make everything perfecto for you.
妈妈，我跟你说过了。我们都是成年人了，我们想为自己的婚礼买单，这样婚礼就能成为我们想要的。
Mom, I've told you. We are adults and we wanted to pay for our own wedding so it could be what we wanted.
这就是你想要的?
And this is what you wanted?
那是印刷错误。
That was a printing error.
♪甚至比你崇拜的任何人都重要
♪ E is even more than Anyone that you adore ♪
♪爱是我能给你的一切♪
♪ And love is all That I can give to you ♪
爱情不仅仅是两个人的游戏
♪ Love is more than Just a game for two ♪
两个相爱的人也能做到♪
♪ Two in love can make it ♪
♬爱是为你和我而生的
♪ Love was made For me and you ♪
嗬! !
Hoy!
哦!哦!
Oh! Oh!
哦!嘿!
Oh! Hey!
哦，我差点开枪打你!
Oh, I almost shoot you!
我以为你是个海盗，但你只是个普通人。
I thought you're a pirate but you're just a guy.
这是给你新娘的，对吧?
Ah, this is for your bride, huh?
是啊，想给她个惊喜。
Yeah, trying to surprise her.
我在Etsy上看到过类似的东西，看起来很完美，但现在我不太确定了。
I saw something just like it on Etsy, and it looked perfect, but now I'm not so sure.
我想浪漫一点，但又不太老套。
Now, I wanna be romantic but not too corny.
这两者之间只有一线之隔。
There's a really fine line between the two.
你不是应该在那边吗?
Aren't you supposed to be over there?
你的彩排派对。
Your rehearsal party.
哦，天哪!
Oh, my God!
我需要你和你父亲的瑜伽老师谈谈。
I need you to talk to your father's yoga teacher.
——女友?-是啊，随便吧。
- Girlfriend? - Yeah, whatever.
她一直对我微笑。
She keeps smiling at me.
你能告诉她别对我笑了吗?
Can you tell her to stop smiling at me?
是的,妈妈。
Yes, Mom.
我会告诉爸爸的女朋友别对你笑了。
I will tell Dad's girlfriend to stop smiling at you.
这不会引起任何问题。
That won't cause any issues.
还有，我不能和汤姆的妈妈坐在一张桌子上。
Also, I cannot sit at a table with Tom's mother.
在这里的船上，她试着跟着唱《南太平洋》。
On the boat here, she tried to start a sing-along to South Pacific.
她很兴奋。好吗?
She's excited. Okay?
她以前从没出过国。
She's never been out of the country before.
什么样的成年女性从未出过国?
What kind of a grown woman has never left the country?
求你了，妈妈，这两天，你能不能和…卡罗尔!
Please, Mom, for two days, can you just get along with... Carol!
♬我要把那个男人从我的头发里洗掉
♪ I'm gonna wash that man Right outta my hair ♪
♬送他上路♬
♪ And send him on his way ♪
自从汤米宝宝从我肚子里被割出来我就一直期待这一刻。
I've been looking forward to this moment ever since baby Tommy was cut out of my abdomen.
天啊，我还从没去过私人岛屿呢。
Oh, my God, I have never been on a private island before.
我从来没去过一个岛。
I've never been even on an island before.
事实上，你知道吗?这不是真的。
Actually, you know what? That's not true.
我和海伯曼一家一起去的。我们去了麦基诺，在他们搬到布卢明顿之前。
I went with the Heibermans. We went to Mackinac, you know, before they moved to Bloomington.
你去过麦基诺吗，瑞娜塔?
Have you ever been to Mackinac, Renata?
我不知道那是什么，也不知道你刚才说的大部分话。
I don't know what that is or most of the words you just said.
她会很喜欢吗，拉里?
Wouldn't she just love it, Larry?
哦。嗨,达西。
Oh. Hi, Darcy.
嗨,拉里。
Hey, Larry.
我没看到你在那儿。
I didn't see you there.
-嗨。-你好，瑞娜塔。
- Hi. - Hi, Renata.
你猜怎么着?我们给你准备了礼物。
Guess what? We got you a gift.
-你不用这么做的-是的，我们做了。
- Oh, you didn't have to. - Yes, we did.
明天是我们人生中最重要的一天。
It's the biggest day of our lives tomorrow.
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
-快点，打开它。——好的。
- Come on, open it. - Okay.
-拉里，她要开门了。-我明白…哦。
- Larry, she's opening. - I get... Oh.
Ah-uh-huh。
Ah-uh-huh.
哦。有人把它落在浴室了。
Oh. Someone just left that in the bathroom.
你真是我的救命恩人，玛姬。
Oh, you're a lifesaver, Margy.
真不敢相信我迟到了。
I cannot believe I'm late for this.
客人们已经在一起了，你的达西正在和两位母亲说话。
The guests are already mingling, and your Darcy is talking to both the mothers.
哦,不。走了。走，走，走，走，走。
Oh, no. Go. Go, go, go, go, go, go.
哦!
Oh!
你给我女儿买了生锈的刀?
You got my daughter rusty knives?
这是你“借来的东西”。
It's your "something borrowed."
我们家每个人结婚那天都要用。
Everyone in our family uses them on their wedding day.
给你带来一生的好运。
Brings you a lifetime of good luck.
除了格雷格叔叔他被铲车砍了头。
Except for Uncle Greg who ended up getting decapitated on that forklift.
但这不是刀的错。
But that's not the knife's fault.
达西!
Darcy!
爸爸!
Dad!
——谢谢。毫米。
- Gracias. - Mm.
卡罗尔，你看起来很可爱。
Carol, you look lovely.
毫米,毫米。
Mm. Mm.
拉里，你好，先生。
Larry, hello, sir.
——嘿!-我也要吻你
- Hey! - I'm gonna kiss you too.
——哦。毫米。
- Oh. - Mm.
——对不起。做了什么?-好吧。
- Sorry. Done? - Yeah, okay.
Renata。
Renata.
罗伯特。
Roberto.
我很高兴你们俩还是朋友。
I love that you two are still friends.
——躲躲猫!——哦。
- Peekaboo! - Oh.
这就跟你问声好！
Hi!
Mwah。Mwah。
Mwah. Mwah.
毫米!
Mm!
达西，我很荣幸能在这神圣的仪式上见证重生和忠诚。
Oh, Darcy, I am so honored to bear witness to this sacred observance of rebirth and devotion.
——相同。-谢谢。
- Same. - Thank you.
Renata。
Renata.
我要去一下女厕。
I need to go to the ladies' room.
嘿，我也是。
Hey, me too.
当我穿着正装的时候，我喜欢站着尿尿。你呢?
When I'm in formal wear, I like to pee standing up. How about you?
——对不起。-没关系。
- Sorry. - That's okay.
谢谢你，玛吉。
Thank you, Margy.
哦,嘿。
Oh, hey.
-嗨。-你好吗?
- Hey. - How are you?
——哦。-我的天啊。
- Oh. - Oh, my God.
-这是给你的。——谢谢。
- That's for you. - Thanks.
大的爸爸。
Big papi.
我的男人。Mwah。
My man. Mwah.
——这…我只是…-很高兴见到你，爸爸。
- This... I just... - Nice to see you, Dad.
——先生。-我们暂时还是叫罗伯特吧
- Señor. - Let's just, uh, stick with "Robert" for a little while.
——正确的。罗伯特。-汤姆，我听说是你发现了这个不可思议的度假村。
- Right. Robert. - Tom, I heard you were the one who found this incredible resort.
-是的。我做到了。——是的。
- Yeah. I did. - Yes.
我其实是研究生物共振的，这地方充满了能量振动。
I actually study bioresonance, and this place is teeming with energetic vibrations.
-嗯-就像我们的房间里到处都是虫子
- Mm. - It's just like our room teeming with bugs.
四季酒店本来不错，但你不想让我帮忙，所以…有些东西比钱更重要，爸爸。-是的。
The, uh, Four Seasons would've been nice, but you didn't want my help, so... Some things are more important - than money, Dad. - Yeah.
这是有争议的。
That's debatable.
我想再喝一杯。
Well, I need another drink.
是的。
Yeah.
不，我很好。谢谢。
No, I'm good. Gracias.
好吧,嗯…我很好。
Okay, well... I'm fine.
他会喜欢我吗?
Is he ever gonna like me?
是的，只要你冷静下来，表现得像你自己。
Yes, if you just chill out and start acting like yourself.
天啊，我们的家人真多。
God, our families are a lot.
-什么意思?-你去哪儿了?
- What do you mean? - And where have you been?
我刚完成一个小项目。
I was just finishing up a little project.
我错过了什么?
What'd I miss?
你妈妈给了我诅咒刀。
Oh, well, your mom gave me cursed knives.
然后我妈差点冲我爸的女朋友吼因为她笑了。
And then my mom almost yelled at my dad's girlfriend for smiling.
——哦。-还有，你表姐艾米问我哪里可以给振动棒充电。
- Oh. - Oh, also, your cousin, Amy, asked where she could charge her vibrator.
哦，艾米表妹来了?
Oh, so, Cousin Amy came?
她很快就会的。
She will soon.
嗯，你穿的是什么?
Um, what are you wearing?
哦，这是，呃…你的头发怎么都湿了?
Oh, it's, uh... Why is your hair all wet?
哦,我……我只是…我…我在月光下游了个泳。
Oh, I... I just... I... You know, I went for a little moonlight swim.
你掉进水里了，是吗?
You fell in the water, didn't you?
是的，我掉进水里了。
Yeah, I fell in the water.
你知道吗，你这么不会撒谎还挺可爱的。
You know, it's kinda cute how bad you are at lying.
只是…答应我…答应我，今晚都别放开我的手，好吗?
Just... Just promise me... Promise me, you won't let go of my hand for the rest of the night, okay?
我保证。
I promise.
Ace。
Ace.
艾斯刚放了蜜月歌单。我需要改变它。
Ace just put on the honeymoon playlist. I need to change it.
用"需要"这个词对吗?
Well, is "need" the right word?
-爸爸，求你了。-是啊。
- Dad, please. - Oh, yeah.
汤米，汤米，我需要你，就五分钟。
Tommy, Tommy, I need you for, like, five minutes.
——什么?不，不，不。-紧急情况
- What? No, no, no, no. - It's an emergency.
我一直在准备伴郎致辞，对吧，进展得很顺利。
I've been working on my best-man speech, right, and it is going really well.
-嗨。-嗨。
- Hi. - Hey.
爸爸的女朋友刚问我爱的语言是什么。
Dad's girlfriend just asked me what my love language is.
她很糟糕。
She sucks.
二十年来我见你最开心了。
Happiest I've seen you in 20 years.
——谢谢。——干杯。
- Thanks. - Cheers.
爸爸邀请了你的前任?
Dad invited your ex?
上帝!他是怎么变得越来越热的?
God! How does he just keep getting hotter?
看来他要去看色情电影了。
Looks like he's leading a porn safari.
我本不想邀请他，但爸爸坚持说巴厘岛很近。
I didn't wanna invite him, but Dad insisted because he said Bali was so close.
哇。哇，哇，哇。哇,哇。
Wow. Wow, wow, wow. wow, wow.
老爸就是个爱惹是生非的贱人。
Dad is a messy bitch who loves the drama.
他从来没回复过，所以我们以为没事了。
Well, he never RSVP'd, so we thought we were in the clear.
我没想到他真的来了。你知道，他从来没有回复过。
I didn't think he'd actually come. You know, he never RSVP'd.
不，这是个非常非常酷的举动。见到他我真的很兴奋。
No, that's a very, very cool move. I'm really excited to meet him.
哦，看起来他很着急，忘记把衬衫扣子扣上了。
Oops, looks like he was in a rush and forgot to button his shirt all the way up.
蒂蒂。
Deedee.
-嘿，伙计，你好吗?-嗨。
- Hey, man, how are you? - Hey.
嗨,肖恩!
Hi, Sean!
很抱歉我迟到了。
I am so sorry that I'm late.
你爸爸在最后一刻要我去日本，然后，你知道，我不得不从京都租了一架飞机，就像整件事一样。-不，没关系。我们只是…
Your dad needed me to go to Japan at the last minute, and then, you know, I had to charter a jet from Kyoto, - just like a whole thing. - No, it's okay. We just...
我们不知道你要来。
You know, we didn't know you were coming.
你爸爸和我想给你个惊喜。
Your dad and I wanted to surprise you.
宝贝，你知道我无论如何都不会错过你的婚礼的，对吧?
Look, babe, you know I wasn't gonna miss your wedding for anything in this world, right?
-肖恩，这是汤姆。——汤姆。
- Sean, I want you to meet Tom. - Tom.
-哦，嘿!——汤姆!
- Oh, hey! - Tom!
-汤姆，汤姆，汤姆。——肖恩。是的。
- Tom, Tom, Tom. - Sean. Yeah.
-很高兴认识你。-嘿，汤姆。
- Nice to meet you. - Hey, Tom.
伙计，我一直很想见见迪迪的球员。
Man, I have been dying to meet Deedee's ball player, man.
你踢什么位置?
What position you play?
-我是…好吧,我……-他是指定击球手。
- I'm a... Well, I... - He's a designated hitter.
不幸的是，他们没有签他的合同，所以严格来说，他失业了，但是…40岁从未成年球员中被裁掉。
Uh, unfortunately, they didn't pick up his contract, so, technically, he's unemployed, but... Cut from the minors at 40.
汤姆，这是一个艰难的突破。但如果你保持乐观，你在教练这一行会有很好的前途。
That's a tough break, Tom. But if you stay positive, you could have a really great future in coaching.
你懂我的意思吗?
You know what I mean?
是的。
Yeah.
这是个好主意。
That is an excellent idea.
-我想是的。-谢谢。
- I think so. - Thank you.
是的。
Yeah.
该吃晚饭了吗?
Is it time for dinner?
你们不远万里来到这里，我们很感动。
We are so very touched that you all made the trek out here.
我们真的想选一个你们都不方便的地方。
You know, we really wanted to pick a place that was convenient for none of you.
你知道吗，我在律所话太多了。
You know what, I talk too much at the law firm.
所以我要把它交给风云人物，是他成就了这个周末，我可爱的汤姆。
So I am going to hand it over to the man of the hour, the guy who made this whole weekend happen, my lovely Tom.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
-去吧!-加油，姑娘!
- Do it! - You go, girl!
嗯…——是的!-你能行的。
Uh... - Yeah! - You got this.
对吧?
Right?
我可以即兴发挥，对吧?
I can just wing this, right?
达西说了很多关于，她在巴厘岛和平队的日子，我就想，如果我们在那里结婚该有多酷。
Darcy talked a lot about, uh, her time in the Peace Corps in Bali, and I thought, you know, how cool would it be if we got married there.
然后，我意识到巴厘岛的物价不像巴厘岛那样高。
And then, I realized that Bali was un-Bali-vably expensive.
我认为菲律宾更好。
I think the Philippines are better.
Ace?
Right, Ace?
Ace表示同意。下一个。
Ace agrees. Next.
哦!
Aw!
我知道你们很多人都见证了我的求婚。
I know a lot of you were there to witness my proposal.
震惊和惊喜。无价的。
The shock and surprise. Priceless.
不管怎样，爸爸妈妈，我只想说谢谢你们。
Anyway, Mom and Dad, I just wanna say thank you.
你们的承诺是我们所期待的。
Your commitment is something that we can only aspire to.
-我的天啊。-罗伯特，雷娜塔，我们希望我们的婚姻不像你们的。
- Oh, my God. - Robert, Renata, we hope our marriage is nothing like yours.
主,宝贝。主。
Pivot, baby. Pivot.
我是说，这不是…无论如何，都是一种性格判断。
I mean, that's not a... a character judgment, by any means.
我是说，50%的婚姻都以离婚告终，对吧?
I mean, 50% of marriages end in divorce, right?
哈!太棒了。
Ha! Wonderful.
欢呼,每一个人。
Cheers, everybody.
-干杯，干杯，干杯。——干杯。
- Cheers, cheers, cheers. - Cheers.
我的天啊。这并不顺利。
Oh, my God. That did not go well.
不，那太棒了。
No, that was awesome.
我和迪迪是在巴厘岛的和平队认识的。
So Deedee and I met in the Peace Corps in Bali.
有一天，我们必须把这些医疗用品运到这个村庄。
And one day, we had to run these medical supplies to this village.
我决定教她如何划船，这样我可以睡觉，她可以做所有的工作。
I decided to teach her how to drive the boat, so I could sleep and she could do all the work.
这姑娘第一次开车，就被海岸警卫队开了张超速罚单。
The first time our girl gets behind the wheel, she gets a damn speeding ticket from the coast guard.
对吧?迪迪做事从不半途而废。
Right? Deedee doesn't do anything half-assed.
她知道自己想要什么，就会去追求，而且她不会退让。
She sees what she wants, she goes after it, and she doesn't settle for less.
这是真的，是真的。
It's true, it's true.
你们有些人可能知道，我和迪迪100年前订婚了。
So, as some of you may know, Deedee and I were, 100 years ago, were engaged.
但她取消了约会。
But she called it off.
不。不，不，不。
No. No, no, no, no.
她在等汤姆。
She was waiting for Tom.
那家伙一定是百万分之一的超新星才能抓住那个美丽的灵魂。
And that guy right there has gotta be a one-in-a-million supernova to snag that beautiful soul.
谢谢。
Thanks.
-谢谢，肖恩。-总之，我只想对你说一件事，迪迪。
- Thanks, Sean. - So, in conclusion, I just wanna say one thing to you, Deedee.
卡图卡卡奇。
Katuk kak ci.
是什么……什么?
What's... Katuk kak what?
哦,上帝。这很难解释。
Oh, God. Um, it's hard to explain.
其实意思是"去你爷爷的"它只是…这也不难解释。
It actually means, um, "Fuck your grandpa. " It's just... Well, that's not that hard to explain.
是啊，我也不知道。只是，在巴厘语中，这是非常无礼的。
Yeah, well, I don't know. Just, in Balinese, it's super offensive.
是啊，这在哪里都很无礼，不是吗?
Yeah, well, it's offensive everywhere, no?
-是的。我的意思是……它只是…-“去你爷爷的!”
- Yeah. I mean... It just... - "Fuck your grandpa!"
-它只是让我们发笑。-很有趣。
- It just made us laugh. - It is funny.
嗨,大家好。
Hi, everybody.
我是汤姆的小妹妹，珍妮。
I'm Tom's baby sister, Jeannie.
-是的，Jeannie!-嘿，珍妮!
- Yeah, Jeannie! - Hey, Jeannie!
肖恩的演讲，是不是很精彩?
Wow, Sean's speech, wasn't it somethin'?
亲爱的?
Honey?
也许我们今晚就到此为止吧。
Maybe we should just, you know, call it a night.
不，宝贝，你去吧。
No, babe, you go ahead.
既然肖恩决定要来，我得把餐桌中心装饰好重新安排座位表。
I gotta finish these centerpieces and rearrange the seating chart now that Sean decided to show up.
汤姆!
Tom!
我们做爱吧。
Let's have sex.
是的。是的。
Yes. Yes.
只是…只是…只是…只是给我…只是…我得赶紧吃完这些菠萝。
Just... Just... Just... Just gimme... Just... I just have to finish these pineapples real quick.
好的。嗯…但你真的必须现在就吃完菠萝吗?
Okay. Um... But do you really have to finish pineapples right now?
我的天啊。我爱穿t恤不穿裤子的你。
Oh, my God. I love you in a T-shirt and no pants.
我要到这儿来，这个高高的架子，这样我就能找点东西读了。
I'm just gonna reach over here, this high shelf, so I can get something to read.
当你够不到高架子的时候为什么这么性感?
Why is it so sexy when you can't reach high shelves?
所以,嗯…对不起，小姐，但那是…-就是这个吗?-不不不。
So, um... I'm sorry, miss, but it was... - It's this one here? - No, no, no.
就是那边的那个。
It's the one over there.
-先生，拜托。-哦，这个。
- Sir, please. - Oh, this one.
-这个。——是的。
- This one. - Yes.
——那?-谢谢，先生。
- That? - Thank you, sir.
好的。很高兴我能帮上忙。
Okay. Glad I could help.
我想你了。
I miss you.
好久不见了，是吧?
It's been a while, huh?
我知道。
I know.
我想你了。
I miss you.
我能问你一个问题吗?
Could I ask you a question?
这是个性感的问题吗?
Is it a sexy question?
嗯…只是想知道你为什么又取消了和肖恩的订婚。
Um... Just wondering why you called off the engagement with Sean again.
这一点都不性感。
That is so not sexy.
我…我告诉过你。
I... I told you this.
我们很年轻，我们在巴厘岛，然后有一天，我醒来，感觉不对劲。
We were young, we were in Bali, and then one day, I woke up and it just didn't feel right.
——好吗?——好的。
- Okay? - Okay.
但你答应了。
But you said yes.
是什么改变了你的想法?
You know, what changed your mind?
我不知道。
I don't know.
呃,他……他开始和我爸爸一起工作，他变了，他只关心地位和金钱。
Uh, he... he started working with my dad, he changed, and all he cared about was status and money.
话说回来，你为什么要在婚礼前夜谈论我的前任?
Anyway, why do you want to talk about my ex the night before our wedding?
我不知道。也许是因为你邀请他参加我们的婚礼?
I don't know. Maybe because you invited him to our wedding?
记住，我没有。
Remember, I didn't.
我爸爸让我邀请他。我该说什么?
My dad asked me to invite him. What was I supposed to say?
我不知道。呃,不是吗?
I don't know. Uh, no?
如果你没记错的话，我不想邀请任何人。
If you remember correctly, I didn't wanna invite anyone.
我想私奔。
I wanted to elope.
我同意传统婚礼的唯一原因是你说我们可以独处。
The only reason I agreed to a traditional wedding was because you said that we'd have moments alone.
嘿,你好。这是卡罗尔。
Hey, hello. It's Carol.
嗨。你好。
Hi. Hello.
你未来的岳母，卡罗尔。
Your future mother-in-law, Carol.
是的，我知道你的名字，卡罗尔。
Yep, I know your name, Carol.
我带了一些用来做欢迎包的多余的东西以防你想给肖恩做一个。
I brought some of the extras for the welcome bags in case you want to make one for Sean.
哦!哦。
Oh! Oh.
太好了。谢谢。
Great. Thanks.
好的，谢谢。
All right, thanks.
汤米，她没穿裤子。
Tommy, she's not wearing any pants.
我只是想问问…我希望你不会介意
I just want to ask, and... and I hope it's okay.
这是遗传，还是普拉提之类的?
Is that genetics, or is it, like, Pilates or something?
妈妈，现在不是说这个的时候。
Mom, now is not the time for this.
是的，好的。但是，我们得把你弄出去。
Yes, all right. But, you know, we need to get you outta here.
这是你婚礼的前一天晚上，你们不能在一起过夜。
It's the night before your wedding, and you can't spend the night together.
-不，妈，只是…-你不能。这会带来坏运气的。
- No, Ma, it's just... - You can't. It's bad luck.
他的表妹珍娜，她昨晚和她丈夫在一起。
You know, his cousin, Jenna, she spent the night with her husband.
你瞧，她得了莱姆病，现在不能穿凉鞋了。
Lo and behold, she got Lyme disease, and now she can't wear sandals.
这是传统。
It's a tradition.
哦。看看这对幸福的夫妇。
Oh. Look at the happy couple.
你去哪儿了?
Where have you been?
你应该给我做头发的。
You were supposed to do my hair.
现在鸟要在里面产卵了。
Now birds are gonna lay eggs in it.
我知道。我睡过头了。我很抱歉。
I know. I overslept. I'm sorry.
昨晚算是，算是和里奇上床了。
Kind of, sort of, slept with Ricky last night.
——瑞奇?——是的。我很抱歉。
- Ricky? - Yes. I'm sorry.
我只是，我想要一些东西，你知道，不太对。
I just, I was in the mood for something, you know, that wasn't quite right.
比如在寿司店点汉堡什么的。
Like ordering a hamburger at a sushi bar or something.
我今天要避开他。它很好。
I'm just gonna avoid him today. It's fine.
他是汤姆的伴郎。
He's Tom's best man.
你们俩得一起走上红毯。
You two have to walk down the aisle together.
我很擅长无视身边的人。
I am very good at ignoring people that I'm standing next to.
-不是开玩笑。——准备好了吗?
- No kidding. - Ready?
真不敢相信你居然同意穿卡萝尔的婚纱。
I can't believe you agreed to wear Carol's wedding dress.
好的。
Okay.
好吧,好吧。
Okay, okay.
无论如何，你看起来都很美。
You look beautiful, no matter what.
她准备好了!
She's ready!
我们要不要来一轮龙舌兰?
Hey, should we all do a round of tequila shots?
我在裙子上加了防溅剂，尽量别吸入化学物质。
Well, I Scotchgarded the dress, so try not to inhale the chemicals.
面纱在哪里?面纱在哪里?
Where's the veil? Where's the veil?
好的。
Okay.
是的，龙舌兰酒。
Well, yes, tequila.
除非我们拿到瓶子，否则我不准备好。
Unless we get the bottle, I'm not set.
不，不喝龙舌兰。
No, no tequila.
哦!
Oh!
她们中最漂亮的。
The prettiest of them all.
你看起来比我们其他人好多了。
You look so much better than the rest of us.
这件衣服真漂亮。
This dress is just wonderful.
我在婚礼上穿过，珍妮在她的婚礼上穿过，现在你也要在你的婚礼上穿过。
I wore it for my wedding, Jeannie wore it for hers, and now you're gonna wear it for yours.
哦，天哪。
Oh, my gosh.
看看你。
Look at you.
这是用组织做成的白珊瑚。
Oh, it's white coral made out of tissue.
嗯…有些事情，你知道，感觉不对。
Um... Something doesn't, you know, feel right.
你觉得如果我们把面纱吹干，它会更蓬松吗?-好吧，我现在看到的是，我觉得左胸实际上稍微低一点
Do you think if we blew-dried the veil, - it would be more fluffy? - Okay, so what I'm seeing is, I think that the left boob is actually slightly lower
-而不是右胸。-像这样，像这样?
- than the right boob. - Like floof, floof, like that?
昨晚我身上发生了一些神奇的事。
Hey, something kinda magical happened with me last night.
理论上说……如果我们娶了姐妹会很奇怪还是很美好?
Theoretically speaking... would it be weird or wonderful if we married sisters?
是的,当然。
Yeah, sure.
嘿，嘘，拉里。汤姆很无聊。
Hey, psst, Larry. Tom's being boring.
来拍我后空翻!
Come film me doing a backflip!
哦,我……我觉得我不应该走路。
Oh, I... I don't think I should walk.
好吧。
All right.
它的时间。
It's time.
哇!
Wow!
看看你。
Look at you.
好的。
Okay.
你想谈谈。
You wanted to talk.
我知道现在是最后时刻。
I know it's last minute.
我只是…
I just...
我讨厌昨晚的结局，而且…我不希望我们的婚礼一开始就不顺利。
I hated the way things ended last night, and... And I didn't want our wedding day to start off on a bad note.
我的天啊。
Oh, my God.
天啊，我以为你要取消了。
God, I thought you were calling it off.
取消婚礼?
Calling off the wedding?
——为什么?-我不知道。
- Why? - Uh, I don't know.
我是说，这个周末跟计划不太一样。
I mean, this weekend hasn't exactly gone to plan.
你和我过去几个月的争吵比我们在一起的头四年还多。
You and I have been arguing more in the last few months than we did our first four years together.
我不知道。我以为婚礼应该很有趣。
I don't know. I guess I thought weddings were supposed to be fun.
哦。好的。
Oh. Okay.
我很抱歉没能让你的婚礼更有趣。
Well, I'm sorry I didn't make your wedding more fun for you.
嗯,没有。这是……达西，这不是…
Well, no. That's... Darcy, that's not what...
这不是我的婚礼。这是我们的婚礼。
And it's not my wedding. It's our wedding.
几乎没有。
Hardly.
是的,汤姆。
Yeah, Tom.
你太关注婚礼了你变成了另一个人。
You got so fixated on the wedding that you... you turned into a different person.
我很抱歉。我只是希望一切都完美。
I'm sorry. I just wanted everything to be perfect.
为什么这对你这么重要?
Why is that so important to you?
为什么它对你不重要?
Why isn't it important to you?
就好像你根本不在乎婚礼一样。
It's like you don't even care about the wedding.
好吧,我……我当然在乎。
Well, I... Of course I care.
噢,是吗?
Oh, yeah?
是你坚持要我们为婚礼埋单的。
You're the one that insisted that we pay for this wedding.
可是我是那个跟供应商讨价还价的人什么都搞砸了，而你却一直在说"我不知道。看起来不错。”
Yet I'm the one that's bargaining with all the vendors and DIY-ing everything, and all you're saying is, "I don't know. It looks good,"
你知道，“听起来不错，汤姆。你想要什么都行。”
you know, "Sounds good, Tom. Whatever you want."
我告诉过你我不想要一场盛大的传统婚礼。
I told you that I did not want a big traditional wedding.
好吧?我不是什么娇羞的新娘。我是个成年女人了。
Okay? I'm not some blushing bride. I'm a grown woman.
我不想让我爸陪我走红毯。
I don't want my daddy walking me down the aisle.
我不需要大公主裙，当然也不需要结婚登记簿。
I don't need a big princess dress, and I certainly don't need a wedding registry.
我的东西已经准备好了。我喜欢我的东西。
I have my things already. I like my things.
我想要一台Roomba。
I wanted a Roomba.
她不在大厅里。
Well, she's not up in the lobby.
我的电话打不通。
I can't get through on my phone.
我的天啊。他们掉进沟里了。
Oh, my God. They've fallen in a ditch.
什么?你怎么知道的?
What? And how do you know that?
我不知道。
I don't know.
我对这种事有第六感。
I just have a sixth sense about these things.
艾斯和我去四处看看。
Ace and I will take a look around.
别担心。我们会找到他们的。
Don't worry. We will find them.
检查所有沟渠!- - -神。
- Check all ditches! - God.
我希望只有你和我在大海中央。
I wanted it to just be you and me in the middle of the ocean.
我说了400遍，那会害死我妈妈的。
And for the 400th time, that would've killed my mother.
啊。正确的。
Ugh. Right.
所以我才会穿着你妈妈的裙子头上还多了十磅头发。
And that's why I'm in your mother's dress with an extra 10 pounds of hair on my head.
但事实是，自从你求婚后我想要的东西你一件也没听进去。
But the truth is, you have not listened to one thing I wanted since you proposed.
好吧，达西，我听着呢。开导我。
Okay, well, Darcy, I'm listening. Enlighten me.
是什么?你想要什么?
What is it? What is it that you want?
汤姆,我们……我们谈过这个。
Tom, we've... We talked about this.
我们第一次约会的时候我就告诉过你，我不想要盛大的婚礼。
I told you on our very first date, I didn't want a big wedding.
我以为你改变主意了。
Well, I thought you changed your mind about that.
那你为什么还同意这么做?
Why did you even agree to do it then?
哦,我……我不…我不知道!
Oh, I... I don't... I don't know!
好吧?因为…因为我爱你。因为我……我w……我想让你幸福。
Okay? Because... Because I love you. Because I... I w... I wanted you to be happy.
走吧!快点，走!
Go! Come on, move!
每个人,动!来吧!
Everybody, move! Come on!
沿着。
Move along.
出去，马上出去。来吧。来吧。
Go outside, go outside right now. Come on. Come on.
如果你不想这么做，现在还不晚。
If you don't wanna go through with this, it's not too late.
什么?
What?
不。我们把所有我们爱的人都带到菲律宾参加我们的婚礼。
No. We brought everybody that we loved down to the Philippines for our wedding.
我穿着这条裙子!我们在做这个!
I'm in this dress! We're doin' this!
哦，太美了。这些是你的誓言吗?
Oh, that was beautiful. Are those your vows?
我的天啊。
Oh, my God.
你说服了自己，我想取消婚礼，现在你却让我取消了。
You convinced yourself that I wanted to call off the wedding, and now you're making it happen.
哦，这就对了。让自己免于承担任何真正的责任。
Oh, there you go. Lawyering yourself out of any real responsibility.
你用戒指划伤了我!
You cut me with your ring!
不会再发生了。
Won't happen again.
太棒了!
Great!
你为什么不去和肖恩在一起?
Why don't you go be with Sean?
也许你们可以去找些老爷们!
Maybe you guys could go bang some grandpas!
我不知道为什么。我有不祥的预感。
I don't know why. I have a bad feeling about this.
会没事的，亲爱的。
It's gonna be fine, honey.
我觉得你可能反应过度了。
I think you might be overreacting.
不要动!趴下，趴下，趴下!
Hold still! Get down, get down, get down!
没有运行!
No running!
——每个人!-下来。
- Everyone! - Get down.
去游泳池!现在!
To the pool! Now!
第一排，开始!
First rows, go!
走，走，走!
Go, go, go!
大家，这边走!这种方式!
Everyone, this way! This way!
来吧!来吧!一行!我们走吧!
Come on! Come on! One line! Let's go!
我们走吧!
Let's go!
达西。
Darcy.
-伙计们，上!-去，去，上去。
- Guys, go! - Go, go, up there.
在那里!在那里!走吧!坚持到底。
Up there! Up there! Go! Go to the end.
-走，走!-大家快走!
- Go, go! - Everybody, walk!
-继续。-走吧。
- Keep going. - Let's go.
走吧!
Go!
继续前进!好了。
Keep moving! There you go.
转弯。转弯。走吧!
Turn. Turn. Go!
-排队。-继续前进。
- Line up. - Keep moving.
排好队，开始!
Line up, go!
——现在!——没有。
- Now! - No.
然后进入游泳池。
And into the pool.
现在。走吧!
Now. Go!
进去。快点，快点，快点。
Go in. Faster, faster, faster.
-下水去。-我们开快点。
- Get in the water. - Let's go faster.
-放下手机。-但我的手机会毁了。
- Drop the phone. - But my phone will get ruined.
我想这就是重点，亲爱的。算了吧。
I think that's the point, sweetie. Just drop it.
是啊，但我有段时间没备份了。
Yeah, but I haven't backed it up in a while.
-放下!——好的。好的。
- Drop it! - Okay. Okay.
没必要害怕。
No need to be scared.
只要大家都听从指示，就没人会受伤。
As long as everybody follows directions, no one gets hurt.
听到你的名字时请举手。
Raise your hand when you hear your name.
罗伯特·里维拉。
Robert Rivera.
罗伯特!罗伯特。
Robert! Robert.
他们在给你打电话。
They're calling you.
非常感谢，卡罗尔。
Thanks a lot, Carol.
-拉里·福勒。——现在。
- Larry Fowler. - Present.
我…我是卡罗尔，他的妻子。
I... I'm Carol, his wife.
这样你就不用跑两次了。
Just so you don't have to make two trips.
等待,等待。我要放在中间。
Wait, wait. I'd like it in the center.
肖恩·霍金斯。
Sean Hawkins.
如果你伤害了泳池里的任何人，你就得对我负责。
If you hurt anyone in this pool, you're gonna have to answer to me.
这是小组的英雄吗?
Is this the hero of the group?
是的。
Yes.
不。我的天啊。
No. Oh, my God.
总会有一个。
There is always one.
好吧。
All right.
新娘和新郎在哪里?
Where is bride and groom?
她在那里她不是新娘吗?
She's there. Isn't she the bride?
哦。不。
Oh. No.
阿曼达认为穿白色去参加婚礼是合适的。
Amanda thought it was appropriate to wear white to a wedding.
我不知道这是规定。
I didn't know that was a rule.
是的，你说了。
Yes, you did.
-你就是个煤气打火机。-是的。
- You're a gaslighter. - Yeah.
你看，这是个问题。
You see, this is a problem.
他们可以报警。如果警察来了，我们就杀了所有人。
They could call police. And if police come, we kill everyone.
我的天啊。
Oh, my God.
好吧，我…仪式开始前，我看到汤姆朝自然步道走去，我注意到他的频率低得危险。
Okay, um, I... I saw Tom headed towards the nature walk before the ceremony, and I noticed that his frequency levels were dangerously low.
我想他临阵退缩了。
I think he's getting cold feet.
汤米临阵退缩?
Tommy has cold feet?
这真的是我们现在应该担心的吗?
Is this really what we should be worrying about at this point?
我是一位母亲。我可以同时担心很多事情。
I'm a mother. I can worry about a lot of things at the same time.
就像拉里的鼹鼠。
Like Larry's mole.
哦，没事的，亲爱的。
Oh, it's fine, sweetie.
-它越来越大了。-散开。
- It's getting bigger. - Spread out.
寻找他们。
Look for them.
嘿，呃，我…我…今天早上我给你发短信了，你都没回。
Hey, uh, I... I... I texted you this morning and I didn't hear anything back.
你是认真的吗?
Are you being serious right now?
不。不。
No. No.
达西!
Darcy!
达西!嘿!
Darcy! Hey!
不，不，不。达西。
No, no, no, no. Darcy.
-达西，我进来了-滚开，汤姆!
- Darcy, I'm coming in. - Fuck off, Tom!
哦，谢天谢地。
Oh, thank God.
听着，我知道你现在在生我的气，但你得让我了解你。
Listen, I know you're mad at me right now, but you have to let me in.
我为什么要生气?我太棒了。
Why would I be mad? I'm awesome.
我在一个热带岛屿上，我在吃液体早午餐，而且我不需要对任何人负责!
I'm on a tropical island, I'm having a liquid brunch, and I don't have to answer to anybody!
天啊，这是不可能的。
Oh, my God, this is not happening.
哦，正在发生，伙计。
Oh, it is happening, buddy.
好吧?等我把头发从头上弄下来，我就去海滩告诉大家你是怎么搞砸的!
Okay? And once I get this hair condo off my head, I'm gonna march down to that beach and tell everybody how you blew this up!
嘘……嘘!
Shh... shh!
你现在真的在嘘我吗?
Are you seriously shushing me right now?
搞什么鬼?
What the fuck?
那是血吗?
Is that blood?
现在没时间流血了。
There's no time for a blood freak-out right now.
别告诉我……外面有海盗，他们把所有人都扣为人质。
Don't tell me... There are pirates outside, and they took everybody hostage.
什么?
What?
-我们得找人帮忙-不，不。不。不。
- We have to get help. - No, no. No. No.
-电话没电了。-还有Wi-Fi。
- The phone is dead. - Oh, the Wi-Fi too.
马姬说北边的手机信号比较好。
Marge said the cell service is better on the north side.
你为什么要选一个没有手机信号的岛?
Why did you pick an island with no cell service?
因为我想让人们活在当下。
Because I wanted people to be present and in the moment.
呀!
Jeez!
我不能呼吸了。我不能呼吸了!
I can't breathe. I can't breathe!
我知道。我也不。
I know. Me neither.
不。我…我真的不能呼吸了。是塑身衣的问题。
No. I... I really can't breathe. It's the shapewear.
请帮我脱下这条裙子。
Please help me get out of this dress now.
现在!
Now!
你能放松点吗?
Would you relax?
你刚才跟我说什么?
What did you just say to me?
我说了一切都会好起来的。
I said everything's gonna be okay.
衣服就像一个谜语。
Dress is like a riddle.
哦!
Oh!
天啊，我穿这裙子会死的!
God, I'm gonna die in this dress!
哦，门锁是从里面开的。
Oh, door latches from the inside.
他会知道我们在这里。
He's gonna know we're in here.
当他进来的时候，他也会知道我们在这里，我们在这里。
He's also gonna know we're in here when he comes in here and we're in here.
他会以为我们在洗澡。
He'll think we're in the shower.
什么……什么?
What... What?
然后在一个更好的时间回来?留个便条?
And come back at a better time? Leave a note?
好吧。
All right.
好的,h……计划是这样的。他进来了，他会以为我们在洗澡，然后我跳出来，把他困在网里。
Okay, h... here's the plan. He comes in, he's gonna think we're in the shower, then I jump out and I trap him in the net.
天啊，这计划太棒了。
Oh, my God, that's an amazing plan.
——是的!——不!
- Yes! - No!
你要在海盗身上撒网吗?
You're gonna throw a net over a pirate?
你试过从网里逃出来吗?
Have you ever tried to get out of a net?
很难从网里出来。
It's very hard to get out of a net.
好的。如何……这个怎么样?我喷了他的眼睛。
Okay. How about... How about this? I spray him in the eyes.
眼睛里的发胶怎么比头上的发网好?
How is hairspray in the eyes better than a net over his head?
等等!是的，那实际上是…这实际上是……喷一下。
Wait! Yes, that's actually... That's actually... You spray that.
我来点火柴。就像火焰喷射器一样。
I'll light the match. It'll be like a flamethrower.
-我是说，没用的!——为什么?
- I mean, it won't work! - Why?
-步骤太多。-只有两步。
- Too many steps. - It's two steps.
这是两步。火焰喷射器,净。
It's two steps. Flamethrower, net.
我跳了出来，把网盖在他头上。我要给他一个惊喜。
I pop out and I put the net over his head. I'll surprise him.
不，汤姆，因为子弹是穿网的!
No, Tom, because bullets shoot through nets!
-严格来说，是的。——技术?
- Technically, yeah. - Technically?
从技术上讲，他不能直接投篮，因为他会被网缠住。
Technically, he won't be able to shoot straight because he'll be all fuckin' wrapped up in the net.
我对天发誓，如果你再说一遍"net"…
I swear to God, if you say "net" one more time...
我的天啊。我的天啊。我的天啊。
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
嘘。火焰喷射器。
Psst. Flamethrower.
我要操死他。
I'm gonna fuck him up.
他妈的!
Fuck!
噢!
Ow!
-没关系!不要紧。-你为什么这么做?
- Never mind! Never mind. - Why did you do that?
没关系!
Never mind!
你说得对。
You were right.
发胶比发胶差多了。
That hairspray was so much worse than the net.
——噢!-起来。
- Ow! - Get up.
好的。
Okay.
-来吧。-别掐我。
- Come on. - Don't strangle me.
-转动你的手臂。-他们还活着。
- Turn your arm. - I have them alive.
等待,等待。什么?
Wait, wait. What?
平房15。来接我。
Bungalow 15. Pick me up.
去收集它们吧。
Go collect them.
然后我们可以开始了。
And then we can begin.
你还好吗，杰米?
You doing okay, Jamie?
我的肚子好像要从屁眼里掉下去了。
My stomach feels like it's gonna fall through my asshole.
但除此之外，我很冷静。
But otherwise, I'm chill.
听着，感到害怕很正常。
Listen, it's normal to feel scared.
但我不会让你和你的家人出事的。的承诺。
But I'm not gonna let anything happen to you or your family. Promise.
嗨,肖恩?
Hey, Sean?
我也感到害怕。
I am also feeling scared.
这是我这辈子最害怕的一次。
Like the most scared I've ever been in my whole life.
就像我刚看了《指环王》一样?
It's like I just watched The Ring, you know?
罗比，宝贝，我要你练习我们在伊萨兰学会的呼吸练习，好吗?
Robbie, baby, I want you to practice the breathing exercise that we learned at Esalen, okay?
我要击中一个压力点。准备好了吗?和…呼吸。呼吸。
I'm gonna hit a pressure point. Ready? And... Breathe. Breathe.
从隔膜开始。
From the diaphragm.
-我想我要吐了。-没关系。你做得很好。
- I think I'm gonna throw up now. - It's okay. You're doing fine.
如果他继续发出那种声音，就开枪吧。
If he keeps making that noise, just go ahead and shoot me.
那对幸福的情侣马上就到。
The happy couple will be here in a second.
让我们进入正题。
So let's get to business.
新娘的父亲在哪里?
Where is the father of the bride?
罗伯特。他又给你打电话了。
Robert. He's calling ya again.
谢谢你,卡罗。
Thanks, Carol.
好吧，你想要什么?
Okay, what do you want?
我们用卫星电话给我同事打电话，然后你把四千五百万美元转到一个银行账户上。
Well, we call my colleague on the satellite phone, and you transfer $45 million to a bank account.
什么?什么?
What? What?
我没有那么多钱。
I don't have that kind of money.
我们在谷歌上搜过你。净资产为6000万美元。
We googled you. Net worth is $60 million.
在确定我女儿是否安全之前，我什么都不会给你。
I'm not giving you anything until I find out if my daughter's safe.
-还有你的女婿。-是的，他也是。
- And your son-in-law. - Yeah, him too.
好的。
Okay.
我可以等两分钟把你的钱都拿走。
I can wait two minutes to take all your money.
这种方式。
This way.
你要菠萝糖吗?
You want some pineapple candies?
是我们买的那个奇怪的欢迎包里的，但我在口袋里找到的。
They're from that weird welcome bag we got, but I found them in my pocket.
不，我不想要你恶心口袋里又湿又松的糖果。
No, I don't want loose, wet candy from your gross pockets.
好的。
Okay.
随便你。
Suit yourself.
好的。好吧，好吧，好吧。
Okay. Okay, okay, okay, okay.
-我饿死了。——没有。
- I'm starving. - No.
-你是个混蛋。——嗯。
- You're an asshole. - Hmm.
天啊，真不敢相信我和你上床了。
God, I can't believe that I had sex with you.
说实话，我也很惊讶。
Honestly, I was pretty surprised by that too.
我父母在我上高中的时候离婚了，我的第一次订婚是场灾难。
My parents, they got divorced when I was in high school, and my first engagement was a disaster.
你呢?你有约会对象吗?
What about you? Are you dating anyone?
你一直想当海盗吗?
Have you always wanted to be a pirate?
别再说了，女士。
No more talk, lady.
对不起，先生们。
Excuse me, sirs.
达西，他们会伤害你的。
Darcy, they're gonna hurt you.
我只是忍不住注意到你们身上有股烟味，我很喜欢。
I just can't help but notice that you guys smell like cigarettes, and I am loving it.
能给我支烟吗?
Is there any way I could bum a cigarette?
我是说，我觉得这可能对…我现在所经历的恐慌和恐惧
I mean, I think it might help with the... the panic and dread I'm experiencing right now.
你什么时候开始抽烟了?
Since when do you smoke cigarettes?
这是……我只是…你都不用解开我的手。
It's... I just... You don't even have to untie my hands.
我是说，我…我不用手也能抽烟。
I mean, I... I can smoke with no hands.
你可以直接放进我嘴里。
You could just put it right in my mouth.
给她一支烟。
Give her a cigarette.
——请。-也许能让她闭嘴
- Please. - Maybe it will shut her up.
对，对，对，这能让我闭嘴。
Yes, yes, yes, it will shut me up.
哦，谢谢。
Oh, thank you.
你们是…最好的
You guys are the... best.
什么?
What?
火!
Fire!
哦，天哪!
Oh, my God!
哦，天哪!火焰喷射器!
Oh, my God! Flamethrower!
哦,我的……看，这就是为什么你只有一个步骤的计划!
Oh, my... See, that's why you only have a plan with one step!
——不!-我的天啊!
- No! - Oh, my God!
-刹车!-我在努力!我尝试!
- Get the brakes! - I'm trying! I'm trying!
悬崖!
Cliff!
——悬崖!悬崖!-我看到了!
- Cliff! Cliff! - I see it!
把它开进停车场!
Get it into park!
我尝试!
I'm trying!
-天啊!哦，天哪!——上帝!
- Oh, God! Oh, my God! - God!
哦，滑出去!
Oh, slide out!
我的衣服!我的衣服，汤姆!
My dress! My dress, Tom!
汤姆，别松手!
Tom, don't let go!
别松手!
Don't you let go!
我困了!我困了!
I'm stuck! I'm stuck!
走吧!
Go!
走了。走，走，走。走，走，走。
Go. Go, go, go. Go, go, go.
快点，做点跟棒球有关的事。
Quick, do something baseball-y.
什么?这一点也不像棒球!
What? This is nothing like baseball!
——下!下来,下来!——操!
- Down! Down, down! - Fuck!
-他没子弹了。——正确的。
- He's out of ammo. - Right.
-冲向他!——什么?
- Run at him! - What?
——走吧。相信我，走吧!-不不不!
- Go. Believe me, just go! - No, no, no!
——手榴弹!-他有手榴弹!
- Grenade! - He has a grenade!
先生!
Sir!
先生,先生。
Sir, sir.
把手榴弹给我，长官，长官!
Give me the grenade, sir. Sir!
长官，把手榴弹给我。先生,先生!
Sir, give me the grenade. Sir. Sir!
Ah-ow。噢!
Ah-ow. Ow!
我的天啊。
Oh, my God.
-他死了吗?-我不知道。
- Is he dead? - I don't know.
你死了吗?
Are you dead?
是啊，他死气沉沉。
Oh, yeah, he's very not alive.
不是活着。哦,男孩。
Not alive. Oh, boy.
——是的!你杀了他!——是的!
- Yes! You killed him! - Yeah!
是的，我杀了他!我杀了他!
Yeah, I killed him! I killed him!
天啊，我杀了个人。
Oh, my God, I killed a man.
我杀了一个人。不。
I killed a man. No.
你感觉如何?
How do you feel?
我觉得……我的天啊。我感觉糟透了。
I feel... Oh, my God. I feel horrible.
-是的。-但很兴奋。
- Yeah. - But excited.
你知道，就像，快乐。我都要拉裤子了。
You know, like, happy. Like, I'm gonna shit my pants.
-是的。-你知道的，不过是好的方面。你知道吗?
- Yeah. - You know, like, but in a good way. You know?
嗯。
Huh.
我的天啊。
Oh, my God.
我要进监狱了。
I'm gonna go to prison.
-我要…——不!
- I'm gonna... - No!
-是的。——没有。这是……它……这是正当防卫。他想杀了我们。
- Yeah. - No. It was... It... It was self-defense. He was trying to kill us.
任何法庭都会…任何法院……你还好吗?
Any court would... Any court... Are you okay?
是的。我很好。我很好。
Yeah. I'm fine. I'm fine.
只是，你知道，我看了看那里，看到了所有的血。
It's just, you know, I looked over there and I saw all the blood.
你知道，我想我看到了一些大脑。
And, you know, I think I saw some brain.
-是大脑的问题吗?-是的。是的。
- Was that brain stuff? - Yeah. Yeah.
所以我要抬头看看天空，然后……这样我就不会晕过去了
And so I'm just gonna look up at the sky and... so I don't pass out.
好的。你知道吗?也许我们应该……我们先离开现场吧。
Okay. Well, you know what? Maybe we should... Let's just step away from the scene.
-别往下看。——好的。
- And don't look down. - Okay.
——好的。-别往下看。
- Okay. - Just don't look down.
他们现在应该到了。
They should be here by now.
沿着路往前走。
Head up the road.
-检查他们。-是的。
- Check on them. - Yeah.
好吧。我们得离开这个岛。
All right. We need to get off this island.
我给我们弄到这个手榴弹可能会有帮助。
Well, it might help that I got this grenade for us.
他想把我们炸飞，但我懂了。
I mean, he was trying to blow us up, but I got it.
我明白了。达西又得一分。
I got it. Another point for Darcy.
好了,达西。
Okay, Darcy.
嗯…你还记得那次我们在高速公路上开车你非常冷静地让我靠边停车吗?
Uh... Do you remember that time that we were driving down the highway and you very calmly told me to pull over?
你等到我们靠边停车才告诉我我头上有只大蜘蛛?
And you waited until we pulled over to tell me that there was a giant spider on my head?
是的。是的。
Yeah. Yeah.
是啊，你真聪明。
Yeah, well, that was very smart.
因为如果你早告诉我，我可能会惊慌失措，把车撞坏。
Because if you had told me before, I might have panicked and crashed the car.
等待。我头上有只蜘蛛吗?
Wait. Is there a spider on my head?
不，不，不，不，不，不。
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
不,不。我告诉你这个故事是因为…当我告诉你我将要告诉你的事情时，我不想让你惊慌。
No, no. I tell you this story because... I don't want you to panic when I tell you what I'm about to tell you.
你的手榴弹没有销子。
Your grenade doesn't have a pin.
-什么意思?——嗯…嗯，是…它是……会爆炸吗?
- What does that mean? - Well... Well, is it... is it... is it gonna explode?
不，不，不，不。不，不，不。
No, no, no, no, no. No, no, no.
你怎么拿就怎么拿。很好。好。
Hold it exactly how you're holding it. Good. Good.
——好的。好的。——嗯。
- Okay. Okay. - Mm-hmm.
那个别针把把手固定住了。
That pin holds the handle on.
但当你松开手雷，手柄就会弹开，引信就会点燃，整个事情就会……繁荣。
But when you let go of the grenade, the handle pops off, which lights the fuse, and the whole thing goes... boom.
你怎么这么了解手榴弹?
How do you know so much about grenades?
视频游戏。
Video games.
那我该怎么办呢?应该……我应该扔吗?
So what should I do? Should... Should I throw it?
我担心的是你不能把它扔得足够远而不把我们炸飞。
Well, my concern is that you won't be able to throw it far enough to not blow us up.
-无意冒犯。- - -神。
- No offense. - God.
那又怎样，我只是…我就拿着这个手榴弹?
So, what, I just... I just hold this live grenade?
这手榴弹现在是我生活的一部分了吗?
This grenade is just part of my life now?
是的，现在，是的，是的，是的。
Yeah, for now, yeah, yeah, yeah.
好吧，计划是这样的。
Okay, here's the plan.
我们去拿把刀。
We're gonna get a knife.
——好的。好吧。-我要切断这些联系，我们要把手榴弹处理掉，然后我们要去码头。
- Okay. All right. - I'm gonna cut through these ties, we're gonna get rid of that grenade, and then we're gonna head down to the docks.
我们要冲向守卫它的海盗，跳上一艘船，去下一个岛求救。
We're gonna bum-rush the pirate guarding it, hop in a boat, and head to the next island for help.
——好吗?-汤姆，那个计划…有太多的步骤。我现在明白了。
- Okay? - Tom, that plan... Has too many steps. I see that now.
你有更简单的吗?
Now, you got a simpler one?
——是的。是的。——什么?
- Yes. Yes. - What?
——是的。好的。-你在干什么?
- Yes. Okay. - What are you doing?
快下来。找到了。
Get down here. Found it.
-找到了。是的。-我们在做什么?
- Found it. Yes. - What are we doing?
-就在这儿。-我们在做什么?
- Right here. - What are we doing?
哦。
Oh.
找手机服务。寻求帮助。
Find cell service. Call for help.
你什么时候把它放进内裤里的?
When did you put that in your underwear?
就在海盗把我们带出小屋之前。
Right before the pirates took us out of the cabana.
因为我是个鬼鬼祟祟的小婊子。
Because I'm a sneaky little bitch.
你这个鬼鬼祟祟的小婊子。
Oh, you are a sneaky little bitch.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
——好的。-我们开始走吧。
- Okay. - Let's start walking.
卑鄙的。狡猾的小婊子。
Sneaky. Sneaky little bitch.
你在考验我的耐心，罗伯特!
You're testing my patience, Robert!
你想要我的钱?我要我的女儿。
Look, you want my money? I want my daughter.
-这是一个简单的谈判。——够了!
- It's a simple negotiation. - Enough!
好吧。
All right.
他们要把他带回来。
They're bringing him back.
移动。
Move.
罗伯特。发生了什么事?你还好吗?
Robert. What happened? Are you okay?
他们没伤害你吧?
They didn't hurt you, did they?
在确定我女儿还活着之前我一分钱都不会给他们。
Well, I'm not giving them a dime till I know my daughter's alive.
结果不太好。
That didn't go over very well.
我担心他们会开始射杀人质。
I'm afraid they're gonna start shooting the hostages.
我不认为他们会那么做。
I don't think they're gonna do that.
这不正是海盗的工作吗?
Isn't that exactly what pirates do?
出来吧，海盗先生!
Come out, Mr. Pirate Man!
我叫卡罗尔·伊莱恩·福勒，我活该。
My name is Carol Elaine Fowler, and I deserve to live.
卡罗尔，你在做什么?
Carol, what are you doing?
我把自己人性化了。
I'm humanizing myself.
我在《早安美国》上看到的。
I saw it on Good Morning America.
如果你在他们面前表现出人性，他们就会让你活着。
If you humanize yourself to them, they let you live.
我是一个妻子。我是一位母亲。
I am a wife. I am a mother.
1998年，我是密歇根州米尔福德的顶级房地产经纪人，2007年又一次。
And I was Milford, Michigan's top realtor in 1998, and again in 2007.
我梦想去爱尔兰。
I dream of going to Ireland.
我大器晚成，直到14岁才长出牙齿。
I was a late bloomer and my teeth didn't come in till I was 14.
请选我。
Please pick me.
我叫珍妮·里德。
My name is Jeannie Reed.
我是个尽职的母亲，但不那么尽职的妻子。
I am a devoted mother and a slightly less devoted wife.
这是我第一次没有孩子的假期，所以我在婚礼前喝了很多香槟，吃了几片大麻软糖，这些组合现在真的要了我的命。
This is my first vacation without my kids, so I drank a lot of champagne before the ceremony, took a couple of weed gummies, and the combination is really killing me right now.
我是阿曼达·沃克。我是教母，也是科技行业的女性。
I'm Amanda Walker. I'm a godmother and a woman in tech.
-我去了…-我是瑞娜塔。
- I went to... - I am Renata.
我来自巴西。
I'm from Brazil.
我有一头漂亮的头发。
I have beautiful hair.
是的。非常漂亮。
Yeah. Very beautiful.
还有什么?
What else?
你是个母亲。
You're a mother.
我是一位母亲。
I am a mother.
我叫里基·西尔弗。
My name is Ricky Silver.
我的很多朋友，他们都成双成对，他们结婚了喝散装茶叶什么的。
A lot of my friends, they're pairing up, and they're getting married and drinking loose-leaf tea and shit.
我还是单身。但是昨晚……我和一个美丽可怕的女人做爱了。
And I'm still single. But last night... I made love to a gorgeous and terrifying woman.
你觉得我很可怕?
You think I'm terrifying?
你吓死我了。
You scare the shit out of me.
我是拉里·福勒。
I'm Larry Fowler.
哦……谢谢你！
Oh... Thank you.
——哦。-别紧张，爸爸。
- Oh. - Oh, easy, Dad.
-别挂电话。是的。-我怎么能…-稳住。-等等。等一等。
- Hold the phone. Yes. - How am I gonna... - Hold it steady. - Hold it. Hold on.
我得把这事从脑子里赶出去。
I just gotta get this thing out of my head.
快把我逼疯了。
It's driving me crazy.
——等待。等一等。只是等待。-你在…你在…你是在往我口袋里塞头发吗?
- Wait. Hold on. Just wait. - What are you... What are you... Are you stuffing a loose wad of hair in my pocket?
是的。一团非常昂贵的定制头发，我想留着。
Yes. A loose wad of very expensive, custom-made hair that I would like to keep.
如果我们能活下来。
If we survive.
有什么好笑的?
What's so funny?
-我只是…-嗷，嗷，嗷!
- I've just been... - Ow, ow, ow!
质疑最近的一切。
Questioning everything lately.
如果婚礼不完美怎么办?如果你父母从来都不喜欢我怎么办?
What if the wedding's not perfect? What if your parents never like me?
棒球之后的生活是什么样子?
What does life look like after baseball?
但我从没想过自己会带着手铐在丛林里走，手里还拿着一颗手榴弹。
But not once did I wonder if I'd be walking handcuffed through the jungle with a live grenade.
哦。你的愿景板上没有海盗追你吗?
Oh. Pirates chasing you wasn't on your vision board?
你是我梦想板上唯一的东西。
Well, you were the only thing on my vision board.
-我来，我来，我来——哦!哦!
- I got it, I got it, I got it. - Oh! Oh!
-明白了吗?明白了吗?-我知道了。我明白了。
- You got it? You got it? - I got it. I got it.
——好的。我明白了。-哦，很好。好的。哦。
- Okay. I got it. - Oh, good. Okay. Oh.
-我们有酒吧。-哦，很好。
- We have a bar. - Oh, good.
好吧。
All right.
-手跟着我。——好的。
- Keep your hands with me. - Okay.
——好的。-打电话求助。
- Okay. - Call for help.
是的。狗屎!这是一去不复返了。
Yes. Shit! It's gone.
好吧，继续努力。
Well, keep trying.
-我想，也许…-我们得再高一点。
- I think, maybe... - We have to go higher.
——什么?——是的。
- What? - Yes.
不是……不。不，不，不。我不喜欢高的。
Not... No. No, no, no. Uh, I don't like higher.
是的，我不……我不认为这东西是按代码建造的。
Yeah, I don't... I don't think this thing is built to code.
——汤姆。——什么?
- Tom. - Anything?
不。来吧。
No. Come on.
-是的。-我们快到山顶了。
- Yeah. - We're almost at the top.
也许我们应该往下走，这样我们就不会那么高了。
Maybe we should go back down so we're not up so high.
现在不要考虑高度。好吧?我们是安全的。
Don't think about the heights right now. Okay? We're safe.
是的。你用"安全"这个词太随便了。
Yeah. You use the word "safe" very loosely.
我的天啊。
Oh, my God.
-全方位服务。完整的服务。-哦，是的。
- Full service. Full service. - Oh, yes.
我有全套服务。
I have full service.
哇，哇，哇。沉默。
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Silence it.
我尝试。
I'm trying.
你的群聊失控了。
Your group chat is out of control.
我不会因为有热情的朋友而道歉。
I will not apologize for having enthusiastic friends.
哦!你把它弄掉了。
Oh! You dropped it.
来吧!
Come on!
-我们得快点。——邮政吗?
- We gotta zip. - Zip?
"拉链"是什么意思?
What do you mean, "zip"?
哦!邮政编码。哦,上帝!
Oh! Zip. Oh, God!
走，走，走。
Go, go, go.
不，我认为我们没有合适的设备。
No, I don't think we have the proper equipment.
他们有枪。
Well, they have guns.
有什么手册吗?
Is there some kind of a manual?
下来!
Come down!
我们需要头盔。我在照片里看到很多头盔。
We need helmets. I see lots of helmets in the photos.
为什么他们看起来很害怕?
And then why do they look scared?
别想那么多。跳!
Stop thinking so much. Jump!
-别尖叫!-天啊!哦，天哪!
- Stop screaming! - Oh, God! Oh, my God!
哇!
Whoa!
汤姆，别放手。
Tom, don't let go.
他妈的!
The fuck!
坚持住，宝贝。等一等。
Hold on, baby. Hold on.
好的。
Okay.
嗯…——是的!——是的!
Uh... - Yeah! - Yeah!
那是什么鬼东西?
What the hell was that?
哦,上帝!
Oh, God!
-天啊!-我们怎么降落?
- Oh, God! - How do we land this thing?
我第一次。我先说。
Me first. I'm gonna go first.
-那我呢?-不，让我来。我第一次。
- What about me? - No, let me. Me first.
我要跳了。我要跳了。
I'm gonna jump. I'm gonna jump.
-好的，好的。-我知道了。我明白了。
- Okay, okay. - I got it. I got it.
我走了!
Here I go!
哦!
Oh!
这些人都有病。
These people are sick.
你去找他们，我来杀他们。
You find them, but I kill them.
你可以娶他，但新娘是我的。
You can have the man, but the bride is mine.
警察，海岸警卫队，他们都在那里。
Police, coast guard, they're all right there.
-我们怎么过去?-我不知道。
- How do we get across? - I don't know.
好吧，我们来玩两真一假的游戏。
Okay, let's all go around and play two truths and a lie.
安静点!
Be quiet!
-卡罗尔。——妈妈。
- Carol. - Mom.
一件容易的事。
Easy.
好吧，来吧。
Okay, come on.
来，来，来。
Come on, come on, come on.
我的天啊。
Oh, my God.
我会解决的。
I'm gonna fix this.
我可怜的妈妈。
My poor mom.
她以为她整个周末都能躲着我爸。
She thought she was gonna be able to avoid my dad all weekend.
我妈妈以前很爱我爸爸。
My mom used to love my dad so much.
他是她的整个世界。
He was her whole world.
当他离开时，她失去了快乐。
Then when he left, she just lost her joy.
我是说，她表现得很强硬，但是…
I mean, she acts tough, but...
她从未真正恢复过来。
she never really recovered.
-达西，对不起…-我知道。
- Darcy, I'm sorry... - I know.
我们必须继续前进。
We have to keep moving.
这到底是什么意思?
What the hell does that mean?
厨房。
Kitchen.
好吧，我们得找把刀。
Okay, we need to find a knife.
——哦。嗯。-什么…什么……你在做什么?
- Oh. Mmm. - What... What... What are you doing?
我饿死了。你今天吃饭了吗?
I'm starving. Have you eaten today?
不，我不饿。
No, I'm not hungry.
是的，你是。你表现得很暴躁。
Yes, you are. You're acting cranky.
——嗯。嗯!嗯。——嗯。
- Mmm. Mmm! Mmm. - Mmm.
嗯，这太好吃了。
Mmm, this is so delicious.
我爱你妈妈。
I love your mom.
好吧，来吧。
Okay, come on.
来吧。噢!简单,容易。
Come on. Ow! Easy, easy.
我不能单手切东西。
I can't cut with one hand.
我没手可切不动。
Well, I can't cut with no hands.
我们得找点别的。
We need to find something else.
好吗?
Okay?
切割塑料的东西。
Something that cuts through plastic.
嗯…
Hmm...
是的。
Yep.
-这是个坏主意吗?-是的。
- Is this a bad idea? - Yeah.
-准备好了吗?——不!
- You ready? - No!
好的。
Okay.
好了。
There you go.
坚持住，坚持住，坚持住!
Hang on, hang on, hang on!
达西，你在拖延时间。
Darcy, you're stalling.
-我知道。-我们能行的。
- I know. - We got this.
——好的。是的。-我们能行的。
- Okay. Yes. - We got this.
-听我数。准备好了吗?——好的。
- On my count. Ready? - Okay.
——是的。-十，九，八…你为什么从十开始数?
- Yes. - Ten, nine, eight... Why are you counting from ten?
这是什么，火箭发射?
What is this, a rocket launch?
好的,很好。四。
Okay, fine. On four.
一、二、三……没人能走到四。
One, two, three... No one goes on four.
-没人能上四。-好吧…嘘!嘘。
- No one goes on four. - All right... Shh! Shh.
——好的。,就…-就像创可贴。-好，好。
- Okay. - Just... - Just like a Band-Aid. - Fine, fine.
——准备好了吗?走了。-就像创可贴。
- Ready? Go. - Like a Band-Aid.
我的天啊。
Oh, my God.
来吧。
Come on.
汤姆!
Tom!
汤姆。
Tom.
我以为你走了。
I thought you left.
什么?
What?
不。
No.
从来没有。
Never.
你妈妈的刀去哪儿了?
Where'd your mom's knife go?
天啊，帮帮我。
Oh, Jesus, help me.
这很好。
That's good.
把那双靴子扔给我。
Throw me those boots.
什么?
What?
我越来越喜欢那件衣服了。
That dress is growing on me.
谢谢。
Thanks.
我想要一些不那么传统的东西。
I wanted something less traditional.
是的。也许玛吉有有线网络。
Yes. Maybe Margy's got a hard line to the Internet.
哇，玛吉喜欢柯基狗。
Wow, does Margy love corgis.
不。该死的。
No. Damn it.
你去那边，我去这边。
You go over there, I'll go here.
-是的。-就在那儿。
- Yeah. - They're right there.
-我该怎么办?-我不知道。
- What do I do? - I don't know.
我不知道。
I don't know.
-哦，玛吉。-这边。
- Oh, Margy. - This way.
走，走，走。
Go, go, go.
好的。我抓住你了。
Okay. I got you.
没关系。没关系。
It's okay. It's okay.
来了。快,快。
Come. Faster, faster.
Ace,马吉·…-这是你的地堡吗?——嗯。
Ace, Margy... - Is this your bunker? - Uh-huh.
-男人洞。-它在旋转吗?
- Man cave. - Is it spinning?
它在为其他人旋转吗?
Is it spinning for anyone else?
你在失血。坐下来。
You're losing blood. Sit down.
-坐下。好的。——绷带。Ace。
- Sit down. Okay. - Bandages. Ace.
我去拿医疗箱
I'll get the medical kit.
把手给我。我要把它包起来。
Give me your hand. I'm gonna wrap it.
不。不，不，不。不。
No. No, no, no. No.
你确定吗?很恶心。
Are you sure? It's disgusting.
是的。
Yeah.
哦。欢呼。
Oh. Cheers.
好的。
Okay.
看起来它有一个襟翼。
Looks like it's got a flap.
它的襟翼松了。
It's got a loose flap.
-听着，只要…——嗯。
- Listen, just be... - Mm-hmm.
只是…只是要小心襟翼。
Just... Just be careful with the flap.
别再说"闪"了，好吗?
Please stop saying "flap," okay?
我完全没事。只是不要说拍打。
I'm totally fine. Just don't say flap.
-有多少?——嗯…两个在大厅。还有几个人和人质在泳池边。
- How many are there? - Uh... Two in the lobby. Couple more by the pool with the hostages.
还有一个在码头边，对吧?
And, uh, one by the dock, right?
但是我们有四个。
But we got four.
你说"得到"是什么意思?
What do you mean, "got"?
让他们不再活着了。
Got them to stop, you know, being alive.
天呐
Holy shit.
是啊，但我们没看到你的员工。
Well, yeah, we didn't see any of your staff, though.
我看到他们被锁在水疗中心。
I saw them getting locked up in the spa.
他们从来不为当地人操心。
They never bother with the locals.
美国人是富有的白痴。没有进攻。
Americans are the rich idiots. No offense.
我只是不明白为什么海盗还在这里。
I just don't understand why the pirates are still here.
上次，他们洗劫了房间。
Last time, they just looted the rooms.
二十分钟过去了。
Twenty minutes, gone.
你说"上次"是什么意思?
What do you mean, "last time"?
去年。
Last year.
菲律宾有2000个岛屿，他们却袭击了我们两次?
Two thousand islands in the Philippines, and they hit us twice?
-这不公平。-等等，等等。
- It's not fair. - Wait, wait.
去年夏天海盗来过这里?
The pirates were here last summer?
你居然让我们在这里举行婚礼?
And you let us have our wedding here?
什么?手鼓。我们谈过了吧?
What? Tom-Tom. We talked about it, huh?
你早就知道了?
You knew about this?
首先，去年夏天没人被杀。
Well, first of all, nobody got killed last summer.
我们都认为这种事情再次发生的可能性非常小。
And we both agreed that the chances of it happening again were very small.
-谁是"我们"?-我和玛吉。
- Who's "we"? - Me and Margy.
我们发了很多邮件，我问了很多尖锐的问题，不是吗?
We e-mailed a lot, and I asked a lot of tough questions, didn't I?
你怎么能不告诉我呢?
How could you not tell me about this?
你没告诉我你对结婚有疑虑，所以…是的，你说得对。我没有。你知道为什么吗?
You didn't tell me that you were having doubts about getting married, so... Yeah, you're right. I didn't. You know why?
因为去年一整年，你什么都在想。
Because all last year, you were in your head about everything.
你以为我爸不喜欢你，所以你开始表现得很奇怪。
You thought my dad didn't like you, so you started acting all weird.
现在我爸爸不喜欢你了。
And now my dad doesn't like you.
你以为罗宾斯家会抛弃你。
You thought the Robins were gonna drop you.
然后你开始打得很糟糕，他们就放弃了你。
And then you started playing badly, and they did drop you.
你以为会有坏事发生，然后你就让它发生了。
You think that something bad is gonna happen, and then you make it happen.
这叫做自我破坏。
That's called self-sabotage.
它是。艾斯，谢谢。
It is. Ace, thank you.
而你对这场婚礼感到兴奋。
And all you were excited about was this wedding.
我知道如果我告诉你我有疑虑，你就会破坏我们的关系。
And I knew that if I told you that I was having doubts, that you would sabotage our whole relationship.
你还是这么做了!
Which you did anyway!
我没有破坏任何东西。
I didn't sabotage anything.
我努力让这场婚礼完美无缺。
I tried to make this wedding perfect.
你儿子肖恩出现的那一天，一切都毁了。
And it all got ruined the day your boy Sean showed up.
这和肖恩没关系。
This has nothing to do with Sean.
这是因为你没有安全感。
This is about your insecurities.
这场婚礼是你试图掌控自己生活的方式，因为你必须掌控一切。
And this whole wedding was your way of trying to get control of your life, because you have to control everything.
这就像你下车来帮我平行停车，而我自己就能行。
It's like when you get out of the car to "help me" parallel park, when I can do it just fine on my own.
是啊，我可不觉得17点的转弯"还好"
Yeah, I wouldn't call a 17-point turn "just fine."
你上个月在Old Navy买的牛仔裤是女式牛仔裤。
Well, those jeans you bought from Old Navy last month were women's jeans.
嗯…我在男装区找到的。
Uh... Well, I found them in the men's section.
他们让你看起来像史蒂薇·尼克斯。
They made you look like Stevie Nicks.
你去年的发型，我很讨厌。
That haircut that you got last year, I hated it.
它让你的头看起来很方。你看起来就像辛普森家族的人。
It made your head look square. You looked like a fucking Simpson.
你说它很时髦。
You said it was chic.
你表现得那么自信，那么坚强，但你只是个害怕的小女孩。
You act so confident, so strong, but you're just a scared little girl.
你害怕在这段关系中全力以赴，因为这意味着你可能会失去一些东西。
You're afraid to go all in on this relationship because it means you might have something to lose.
你知道吗?反正这些都不重要。
Well, you know what? None of it matters anyway.
因为我们爱的每个人都可能死去。
Because everyone we love could die.
因为我。
Because of me.
我想他们在经理家里。
I think they're in the manager's house.
我想他们听到了。
I think they heard it.
为什么?
Why?
他们不再说英语了。
They stopped speaking English.
在这里。把它。
Here. Take it.
不喜欢。汤姆。
Don't. Tom.
我们得离开这里。这条隧道通向哪里?
We need to get out of here. Where does this tunnel go?
这条路直通其他海盗所在的水池。
It leads straight to the pool where the rest of the pirates are.
哦，这不理想。
Oh, that's not ideal.
他们在说什么?
What are they saying?
没有线索。
No clue.
我不知道那是什么语言，但肯定不是菲律宾语。
I don't know what language that is, but it ain't Filipino.
——没有。——没有。
- No. - No.
大家都别动。待在这里。
No one move. Stay right here.
没有人动。
Nobody move.
你在做什么?
What are you doing?
好的。
Okay.
他们知道有人在这里，但不知道我们都在。
They know someone's here, but they don't know all of us are.
你待在这里直到结束。
You stay here until it's over.
汤姆!
Tom!
汤姆!他们会杀了你的。
Tom! They're gonna kill you.
-别这样。-我必须这么做。
- Don't do this. - I have to.
这已经不是我们的事了。这是……整件事都是我的错。
This isn't about us anymore. This is... This whole thing is my fault.
你应该得到更好的。
You deserve better.
等一下,汤姆!
Wait, Tom!
嗯…哦,嘿。
Uh... Oh, hey.
嘿,海盗!
Hey, pirates!
我是汤姆，你们一直在寻找的新郎，我正式投降。
I'm Tom, the groom you guys have been looking for, and I am officially surrendering.
-闭嘴!-好吧。
- Shut up! - All right.
怎么，你不喜欢被称为"海盗"吗?
What, you don't like to be called "pirates"?
当我还是个孩子的时候，我想成为一名海盗，你们真的在做。
I wanted to be a pirate when I was a kid, and you guys are actually doin' it.
——移动。-你活在梦里。
- Move. - You're livin' the dream.
祝贺你。
Congratulations.
他们没有杀他。我的天啊。
They didn't kill him. Oh, my God.
他还活着。
He's still alive.
走吧!
Go!
继续。只是移动。
Keep going. Just move.
汤米。我的天啊。这是汤米。汤米!
Tommy. Oh, my God. It's Tommy. Tommy!
闭嘴!
Shut up!
汤米，达西在哪儿?-闭嘴!
- Tommy, where is Darcy? - Shut up!
是的。你的新娘呢?
Yes. Where is your bride?
我…我不知道。
I... I don't know.
真正的。诚实。我…我…我不喜欢。
Truly. Honestly. I... I... I don't.
为实数。我不…我不…我不知道。
For reals. I don't... I don't... I don't know.
你不会撒谎。
You're a bad liar.
是的，他不太会撒谎。
Yeah, he is a bad liar.
汤姆，如果你知道什么，你能做的就是合作。
Tom, if you know something, the best thing you can do is cooperate.
他们只想要钱。
All they want is the money.
你知道吗?谢谢你，肖恩，一如既往地，为我们讲道理。
You know what? Thank you, Sean, as always, for being the voice of reason.
够了!
Enough!
-好吧，好吧!——好的。
- Okay, fine! - Okay.
我告诉你她在哪。
I'll tell you where she is.
卡图卡卡奇。
Katuk kak ci.
什么?
What?
天呐你对他说了什么?
Holy shit. What did you say to him?
这是个内部笑话，肖恩。
It's kind of an inside joke, Sean.
你能帮我一下吗?我有点头晕。
Can you give me a hand? I'm a little woozy.
“当然,人。来，我抓住你了。
'Course, man. Here, I got you.
哇,哇!哇!
Whoa, whoa! Whoa!
你到底在干什么?
What the hell are you doing?
别动，否则我对天发誓，你会掉一只眼睛的。
Don't move or I swear to God, you'll lose an eye.
汤米，你在做什么?
Tommy, what are you doing?
是你说还是我说?
Are you gonna spill the beans or should I?
什么豆?
What beans?
说出来吧。
Just spill the beans.
肖恩雇了这些人闯进我们的婚礼抢罗伯特的钱!
Sean hired these guys to invade our wedding to take Robert's money!
哇。不，不，不，汤姆。
Whoa. No, no, no, no, Tom.
不，这是真的。
No, it's true.
这是一个很严重的指责，但没关系，因为嫉妒会让我们任何人都变得最好。
That is a serious accusation, but it's okay, 'cause jealousy can get the best of any of us.
哦，不，不，不。我不是嫉妒。
Oh, no, no, no. I'm not jealous.
种。
Kind of.
你把我当成威胁是很正常的因为我和迪迪有过一段超然的感情。
It is completely normal for you to see me as a threat because Deedee and I had something transcendent.
但我不是坏人。
But I am not a bad guy.
而且我和这些海盗一点关系都没有。
And I definitely don't have anything to do with these pirates.
噢,是吗?那我叫他去操他爷爷，他为什么要揍我?
Oh, yeah? Then why did he deck me when I told him to go fuck his grandpa?
只是听。倾听自己的心声。
Just listen. Listen to yourself.
我是用巴厘语说的。这些人不是本地人。
I said it in Balinese. These guys are not local.
他们来自巴厘岛。
They're from Bali.
玛姬说上次当地海盗抢劫后就走了。
Margy said the local pirates just looted and left last time.
他们花了大概20分钟。
It took 'em, like, 20 minutes.
哦,上帝。“最后一次”?
Oh, God. "Last time"?
我们显然是被盯上了。这一切都是计划好的。
We were clearly targeted. This whole thing was planned.
他们知道罗伯特的钱。
They knew about Robert's money.
这一切都说不通，直到我发现了这个。
And none of it made sense until I found this.
里奇，拿上我的…抓住………-是的，是的。-在我前面的口袋里。抓住……我前面口袋里有个信封。
Ricky, grab my... Grab the... the... - Yeah, yeah. - In my front pocket. Grab... There's an envelope in my front pocket.
抓住它!
Just grab it!
好了。
There you go.
啊哈!
A-ha!
慢,慢。走慢。
Slow, slow. Go slow.
你的婚礼请柬?
Your wedding invitation?
是的，但我是从其中一个人那里拿到的。
Yes, but I got it off of one of these guys.
他们是怎么拿到邀请函的?
Now, how did they get that invitation?
-我不知道。——嗯…它必须由一位受邀的客人送给他。
- I don't know. - Uh... It had to be given to him by an invited guest.
那是什么受邀嘉宾呢?嗯?
Now, what invited guest could that be? Huh?
瑞奇,op……打开它。
Ricky, op... open it.
啊哈!
A-ha!
这个混蛋认为参加一个他没有回复的婚礼是合适的!
This asshat thought it was appropriate to show up to a wedding he didn't RSVP to!
他没有回复!
He didn't RSVP!
妈妈，这不是现在的主要问题。
Mom, that's not the main issue right now.
听着，我是个母亲。我可以同时为很多事情感到沮丧。
Look, I'm a mother. I can be upset about a lot of things at the same time.
我觉得，现在，我们应该为一件事难过。
I think, right now, we should be upset about one thing.
-好吧。-肖恩让这些人闯入我们的婚礼这样他就能从他最好的朋友罗伯特那里得到一大笔赎金。
- Oh, okay. - Sean had these guys crash our wedding so that he could get a big fat ransom from his best friend, Robert.
嗯?是啊!
Huh? Yeah!
——鲍勃……鲍勃。——是的!
- Bob... Bob. - Yes!
这是因为我没有给你你想要的投资，对吧?
This is because I didn't give you that investment money you wanted, isn't it?
-是的。-不，不，不是那样的
- Yeah. - No, no, it's not like that.
怎么可能……爸爸。
How could... Papi.
你怎么能相信我会来这里背叛…相信我，罗伯特。相信它。
How could you believe that I would come here and betray ev... Believe it, Robert. Believe it.
-没错。这是正确的。——大便。
- That's right. That's right. - Shit.
看到了吗?看，我告诉过你!我告诉过你!
See? See, I told ya! I told ya!
这些灯笼很复杂。里面有纸条吗?
These lanterns are so intricate. Is there a note in it?
“善待彼此。”
"Be excellent to each other."
——嗯。——嗯。嗯。
- Hmm. - Hmm. Huh.
这是比尔和泰德的精彩冒险。
It's from Bill and Ted's Excellent Adventure.
汤姆想在每个灯笼里放句电影台词，而我…我觉得这很蠢，但其实不是。
Tom wanted to put a movie quote in each one of the lanterns, and I... I thought it was stupid, but it's not.
它是甜的。
It's sweet.
我把一切都搞砸了。
And I messed it all up.
我不知道你们是怎么做到的。
I don't know how you guys do it.
你一定有什么特别的东西。
You must have something really special.
-不太好。——Oi。
- Not really. - Oi.
我是说，它很特别，但不是魔法。
Uh, I mean, it is special but it is not magic.
我们刚发过誓。
We just made a vow.
我们已经把事情搞砸了几千次了。
And we've messed things up thousands of times.
但当我们破坏了一些东西，我们会修复它。
But when we break something, we fix it.
达西，我们和你一起去，但我们不想去。
Darcy, we come with you, but we don't want to.
汤米终于成功了。
Tommy finally made the big leagues.
是啊，我从没听过这个。
Yeah, I never heard that one before.
我知道你没有。
I know you haven't.
-她在哪?-我不知道。
- Where is she? - I don't know.
我不…我…我不…我不知道。
I don't... I... I don't... I don't know.
-你在说谎。-不，我…我…说实话-我不知道。——好的。
- You're lying. - No, I'm... I'm... Honestly, - I don't know. - Okay.
该死的!
God damn it!
-你能不能别这样?-是的。
- Would you stop doing that? - Yeah.
-他还会这么做的。——好。很好。
- He'll do it again. - Fine. Fine.
我在撒谎。
I was lying.
我们分手后，达西和我大吵了一架。
After we cut ourselves loose, Darcy and I got into a fight.
她跳上一辆高尔夫球车，去北部海岸悬崖附近寻找手机信号，然后我…我回来是想救大家。
She hopped in a golf cart to go look for cell reception up by the northern coast near the cliffs, and then I... I came back here to try to rescue everyone.
来吧!
Come on!
好的。
Okay.
我们坐直升机去找她。
We'll take the chopper to find her.
我和你一起去。
I'm comin' with you.
我一整天都看着你把事情搞砸了。
I've been watching you mess this up all day.
这是我的节目了。
This is my show now.
哇，太好了。
Wow, that's really good.
我们现在要按我的方式来。明白了吗?
We're doing this my way now. You got it?
我们需要抵押品。
We need collateral.
找女朋友。
Get the girlfriend.
嘿。来了。
Hey. Come.
——在这里。动!——噢!嘿。
- Here. Move! - Ow! Hey.
哦,不。
Oh, no.
——走吧。动!-拜托，我是双子座。
- Go. Move! - Please, I'm a Gemini.
我很容易受伤。
I bruise easily.
——走吧!——噢!噢!噢!
- Go! - Ow! Ow! Ow!
-我的天啊!——罗伯特?罗伯特!
- Oh, my God! - Robert? Robert!
等我回来，那笔钱最好还在我的账户上。
When I get back, that money better be in my account.
如果不是，她就死了。
And if it's not, she's dead.
我把你当儿子看待。
And I treated you just like a son.
-你现在被汤米缠住了- - - - - -罗伯特。
- You're stuck with Tommy now. - Robert.
-那有什么不对吗?-滚开。
- Well, what's wrong with that? - Fuck off.
不，不，不，不，不。
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
达西……汤姆，你答应过这个周末不离开我的。
Darcy... Tom, you promised you wouldn't leave my side this weekend.
达西，你在干什么?
Darcy, what are you doing?
汤姆,听。
Tom, listen.
我还在生你选海盗岛的气，但我也搞砸了。我应该告诉你的……我有多害怕结婚
I'm still mad at you for picking this pirate island, but I messed up too. I should've told you... how scared I was to get married.
这不公平。
That wasn't fair.
你在海盗岛的婚礼上很努力。
You worked so hard on this pirate island wedding.
好吧，不不不。请不要再这么叫了。
Okay, no, no, no. Please stop calling it that.
我只是担心如果我告诉你
I just worried that if I told you...
我会失去你
that I would lose you.
我不能失去你。
And I can't lose you.
我需要你。
I need you.
好吗?
Okay?
好的。
Okay.
——好的。——好的。
- Okay. - Okay.
这比南太平洋好多了。
This is so much better than South Pacific.
妈妈，爸爸呢?
And Mom, Dad?
哇!
Whoa!
——宝贝。-搞什么鬼?
- Babe. - What the fuck?
你刚刚是开枪打我吗?
Did you just shoot me?
别朝你妹妹开枪了!
Stop shooting your sister!
我不是故意的。这是个错误。我…
I didn't mean to. It was a mistake. I...
妈妈，爸爸，向汤姆道歉。
Mom, Dad, apologize to Tom.
——什么?为什么?——什么?
- What? Why? - What?
感谢你批评他策划的这场美丽的婚礼，感谢你从来没有让他觉得在我们家是受欢迎的。
For criticizing this beautiful wedding that he planned, and for never making him feel welcome in our family.
谢谢你邀请肖恩参加我们的婚礼。
And for inviting Sean to our wedding.
好吧，亲爱的，但我觉得有一个更紧迫的问题…——道歉!
Okay, honey, but I think there's - a more pressing issue... - Apologize!
他是我认识的最好的人。
He is the best person that I know.
如果你再说他一句坏话，我发誓我会像射杀杰米一样杀了你。
And if you say one more bad thing about him, I swear I will shoot you like I shot Jamie.
汤姆，我很抱歉。对不起。
Tom, I'm sorry. Sorry.
-汤姆，对不起。对不起。-我们爱你。
- Tom, sorry. Sorry. - We love you.
-哦，嘿，没事-你是我见过最好的人-没关系。我爱你。
- Oh, hey, it's fine. - You're the best person - I've ever met. - It's okay. I love you.
-我们像爱家人一样爱你。-我也爱你。
- We love you like family. - I love you, too.
-好吧。一切都很好。-我爱这个地方。美丽。
- All right. It's all good. - I love this place. Beautiful.
还有，卡罗尔，拉里……我很抱歉!我很抱歉!
And, Carol, Larry... I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
这主要是关于我和我的家人，但我们应该找个时间一起吃午饭。
This was more about me and my family, but we should get lunch sometime.
-我会…-是啊-午餐听起来不错是的。-我们爱吃。
- I would... - Oh, yeah, - lunch sounds great. Yeah. - We love eating.
任何人都很难辜负你完美的婚姻。
It's hard for anyone to live up to your perfect marriage.
谁告诉你我们的婚姻很完美的?
Who told you we had a perfect marriage?
哦，拜托，妈妈。你们打过一次架。
Oh, come on, Mom. You guys fought, like, once.
而是谁更爱狗。
It was about who loved the dog more.
我是说，你们的婚姻有什么不完美的?
I mean, what is not perfect about your marriage?
我和你的玛丽阿姨做爱了。
Well, I made love to your Aunt Marie.
什么?
What?
-是的。-然后我出去和吉姆·罗伯茨做了一些奇怪的性行为。
- Yeah. - Then I went out and started doing all this weird sex stuff with Jim Roberts.
是的。你和吉姆·罗伯茨交往了几个月。——是的。
Yeah. You and Jim Roberts - went on for a couple months. - Yes.
-因为我们的身体刚好合适。-圣…最后，吉姆·罗伯茨不是你父亲。
- Because our bodies just fit. - Holy... In the end, Jim Roberts just wasn't your dad.
玛丽阿姨意识到她有性瘾。
And Aunt Marie realized that she had a sex addiction.
但你知道吗?我们解决了。
But then you know what? We worked it out.
这些都是不可思议的突破，对吧?我的意思是……-给我!
These are some incredible breakthroughs, - right? I mean... - Give me that!
你还记得我吗?
You remember me, huh?
你把我的脸烫了。嗯?
Look, you burn my face. Huh?
是的，我知道。我还是觉得很内疚。
Yes, I know. I still feel really bad about that.
所有人，到泳池里去!现在!
Everybody, in the pool! Now!
到泳池里去!!
Get in the pool! In!
走吧!走吧!
Go! Go!
-你还好吗?——是的。
- Hey, you okay? - Yes.
——是吗?-我们失踪了吗?
- Yeah? - Are we missing people?
是的。看来你儿子肖恩是个混蛋。
Yeah. Turns out your boy Sean's an asshole.
我们找到新娘了。
We have the bride.
听到了吗?
Do you copy?
起来!起来!
Up! Up!
听我说。移动。
Listen to me. Move.
巴厘人吗?这些人是巴厘人?
Balinese? So these guys are Balinese?
肖恩满嘴胡言，他们还把哈里特扣为人质?
And Sean is full of shit, and they took Harriett hostage?
这没有道理。
It doesn't make sense.
为什么肖恩要把哈里特劫持在直升机上她已经被劫持在这里了?
Why would Sean take Harriett hostage on the helicopter when she was already being held hostage here?
我不知道。也许他想多抓她做人质。
I don't know. Maybe he wanted to take her extra hostage.
我觉得哈里特也有份。
I think Harriett is in on it.
——什么?-什么意思?
- What? - What do you mean?
哈里特和肖恩…是恋爱。
Harriett and Sean... are boyfriend-girlfriend.
-哦，得了吧。——恋爱?
- Oh, come on. - Boyfriend-girlfriend?
不,不。看。
No, no. Look.
这是昨晚拍的。
This is from last night.
开始吧。
Here we go.
让我们来看看。
Let's see.
等一下。让我找找看。
Uh, hold on. Let me find it.
哦。哦,男孩。
Oh. Oh, boy.
是的。好了。
Yeah. There you go.
什么?去做吧。说出来。
What? Go ahead. Say it.
罗伯特……
Roberto...
Lo siento。
Lo siento.
谢谢。
Gracias.
没有什么结果。
De nada.
在那里!
There!
肖恩，你保证过这份工作会让我们发财的。
Sean, you promised this job would make us rich.
到目前为止，它只杀了我的四个人。
So far, all it's done is killed four of my men.
伙计，你知道我们能解决的。
Man, you know we can fix this.
交易取消了。我留着钱。
Deal is off. I keep the money.
你就这样离开了。
You walk away with your life.
我不想听。你和我有过约定。
I don't wanna hear it. You and I had an arrangement.
肖恩，理智点。他救了我们。
Sean, be reasonable. He saved us.
-我们很幸运能活着。-你在说什么?
- We're lucky to be alive. - What are you talking about?
听你女人的话。
Listen to your woman.
哦。
Oh.
没关系。这只是一个压力点。放松。
It's okay. It's just a pressure point. Relax.
对着它呼吸。
Just breathe into it.
什么?
What?
带我们下去。
Take us back down.
我们将自己完成这项工作。
We'll finish the job ourselves.
——宝贝。——什么?
- Babe. - What?
-好主意。-是的，我知道。
- Excellent idea. - Yeah, I know.
我什么事都得自己做!
I have to do everything myself!
我们该怎么办?他们随时都会回来。
What are we gonna do? They'll be back any minute.
,就…-嘿，嘿，嘿!
- Just... - Hey, hey, hey!
没有低语。或者我往泳池里扔手榴弹。
No whispers. Or I throw grenade in the pool.
好的。
Okay.
跟我走，好吗?
Go with me, okay?
跟我去吧。
Just go with me.
嘿,每一个人。
Hey, everybody.
我知道现在可能不是最好的时机，但这可能是我们举行婚礼的唯一机会。
Look, I know this may not be the best time, but this may be our only chance to have our wedding.
你说呢，达西?
What do you say, Darcy?
是的,我……我很喜欢。
Yeah, I... I love it.
可以…我们可以做新娘在左边新郎在右边吗?
Can... Can we do bride's side on the left and groom's on the right?
嘿，玛姬，你来主持好吗?
Hey, Margy, will you officiate?
嘿，你能别说了吗?停止它!现在就住手!
Hey, will you stop? Stop it! Stop it now!
等待,等待。如果……如果你让我女儿结婚，我会…我会释放资金。
Wait, wait. If... If you let my daughter have her wedding, I'll... I'll release the funds.
好吧，走吧。
Okay, let's go.
我们走吧。
Let's go.
谢谢,爸爸。
Thanks, Dad.
没事的，小公主。
It's okay, princess.
有些东西比钱更重要。
There are some things that are more important than money.
我不知道是什么，但我想，呃…
I don't know what they are, but I think, uh...
希望你知道自己在做什么。
Hope you know what you're doing.
♬你眼睛里的泪丝
♪ The strands in your eyes ♪
♬他们给自己涂上美妙的颜色
♪ They color them wonderful ♪
♬阻止了我，偷走了我的呼吸♬
♪ Stops me And steals my breath ♪
♬山上的绿宝石♬
♪ Emeralds from mountains ♪
♬来自天空的推力♬
♪ Thrust from the sky ♪
♪永远不会显露自己的深度♪
♪ Never revealing their depth ♪
♪告诉我♪
♪ And tell me ♪
♬我们属于彼此
♪ We belong together ♪
♪用爱的装饰把它装扮起来♪
♪ Dress it up with the trappings of love ♪
♬我会被你迷住
♪ I'll be captivated ♪
♬我会挂在你的嘴唇上♬
♪ I'll hang from your lips ♪
♬而不是绞刑架♬
♪ Instead of the gallows ♪
♬那些悬在上面的心痛♪
♪ Of heartaches That hang from above ♪
♪我会是你哭泣的肩膀♪
♪ And I'll be your cryin' shoulder ♪
♪我将是爱的自杀♪
♪ I'll be love's suicide ♪
♪当我变老的时候我会变得更好♪
♪ And I'll be better When I'm older ♪
♪我会是你生命中最忠实的粉丝♪
♪ I'll be the greatest fan of your life ♪
♪我会是你哭泣的肩膀♪
♪ And I'll be your cryin' shoulder ♪
♪我将是爱的自杀♪
♪ I'll be love's suicide ♪
-♪我也会♪-♪我也会♪
- ♪ And I'll be ♪ - ♪ I'll be ♪
♪老了会更好♪
♪ Better when I'm older ♪
♪我会是你生命中最忠实的粉丝♪
♪ I'll be the greatest fan of your life ♪
♬我将会
♪ I'll be ♪
哇，哇，哇。
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
我想你会后悔的。
I think you'd regret that.
哦!不,不。停止。
Oh! No, no. Stop.
我对手榴弹还是个新手。
I'm fairly new to grenades.
但我很确定如果你开枪打我，这个有弹性的东西会弹开，然后把我们都炸飞。
But I'm pretty sure that if you shoot me, this springy thing pops off, and then this thing blows us all away.
-对吧，宝贝?-没错，宝贝。
- Ain't that right, babe? - That's right, baby.
-不不不。-搞什么…放下枪。
- No, no, no. - What the... Drop the guns.
不。
No.
我扔不了那么远。他不会收到的。
I can't throw that far. It won't reach him.
没人敢动我的家人。
Nobody fucks with my family.
达西?给我一个肉丸子。
Darcy? Give me a meatball.
大便。
Shit.
我知道该去哪里了!
I know where to go!
让我们行动起来!从泳池里出来!
Let's get moving! Out of the pool!
——是的!-来吧!来，来，来!
- Yeah! - Come on! Come, come, come!
从泳池里出来!来吧!
Get out of the pool! Come on!
-是啊，走吧。——马吉·!温泉!
- Yeah, let's go. - Margy! The spa!
在水疗中心很安全!
It's safe in the spa!
他们应该每小时都杀一次人质。
They should've been killing hostages every hour.
杀人有用，肖恩。
Killing people works, Sean.
——操。-给我一次机会说服达西
- Fuck. - Look, give me one chance to convince Darcy.
-好吗?一个。——好。一次机会。
- All right? One. - Fine. One chance.
谢谢你，宝贝。
Thank you, baby.
现在不是时候，肖恩。
This is not a moment right now, Sean.
-走，快点!来吧!-好吧!
- Move, come on! Come on! - All right!
妈妈!妈妈，我们去找人帮忙。
Mom! Mom, we're gonna go get help.
我需要你照顾他们。你能做到吗?
I need you to take care of them. Can you do that?
和卡罗……谢谢你的蛋糕刀。
And Carol... thank you for the cake knife.
我爱死这把蛋糕刀了。
I fucking love this cake knife.
现在只有你和我了。我们走吧。
It's just you and me now. Let's go.
♬是啊♬
♪ Yeah ♪
♬是啊，我现在很敬畏你♬
♪ Yeah, me in awe of you now ♪
♬嗯♬
♪ Hmm ♪
-♪这首歌叫♪-♪无条件的♪
- ♪ This song call ♪ - ♪ Unconditional ♪
-这表明没有奉献♬-奉献♬
- ♪ This show no devotion ♪ - ♪ Devotion ♪
♪让我的心如此敞开♪
♪ Got my heart so wide open ♪
♬提升我的精神像一个圣灵
♪ Lifting my spirit Like a Holy Ghost ♪
-♪所有这一切♪-♪所有这一切爱，爱♪
- ♪ All this ♪ - ♪ All this love, love ♪
-♪不平凡的爱♪-♪平凡的爱♪
- ♪ No ordinary love ♪ - ♪ Ordinary love ♪
♬是啊♬
♪ Yeah ♪
♬啦，啦，啦，啦，啦，啦
♪ La, la, la, la La-la-la-la ♪
♬啊，啦，啦，啦，啦，啦，啦
♪ Ah, la, la, la, la La-la-la-la ♪
♬啦，啦，啦，啦，啦，啦
♪ La, la, la, la La-la-la-la ♪
♬啦，啦，啦，啦-啦-啦-爱♬
♪ La, la, la, la La-la-la-la-love ♪
♬啦啦，啦啦，啦啦，啦啦
♪ La-la, la-la, la-la, la-la ♪
♬啦，啦，啦，啦，啦，啦
♪ La, la, la, la La-la-la-la ♪
♬我需要你在我的臂弯
♪ I need you in my arm ♪
♬是的，是的♬
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♬嘿♬
♪ Hey ♪
♪这一切都没有平凡的爱情
♪ All this no ordinary love ♪
♬爱，爱，爱，爱
♪ Love, love, love, love ♪
♬是啊♬
♪ Yeah ♪
这不是那个步骤太多的计划吗?
Hey, wasn't this the plan with too many steps?
你这么做是为了我?
You did this for me?
这是你想要的吗?
Is this what you wanted?
就你和我在大海中间?
Just you and me in the middle of the ocean?
达西，很抱歉我没听你的。
Darcy, I'm sorry I stopped listening to you.
我只是想如果我策划了完美的婚礼，我们就能拥有完美的婚姻，但是…但这并不存在。
I just thought that if I planned the perfect wedding, we could have the perfect marriage, but... But that doesn't exist.
我是说，看看我父母。
I mean, look at my parents.
我的玛丽阿姨，性瘾者。
My Aunt Marie, the sex addict.
我只想和你在一起。你才是最重要的。
I just wanna be with you. All that matters is you.
我们不需要结婚。
We don't ever have to get married.
如果我们能活下来，我们能不能…我们能重新开始吗?
And if we survive this thing, can we just... Can we start over?
走，走，走，走。
Go, go, go, go.
迪迪，听我说!
Deedee, listen to me!
迪迪，这是个巨大的误会，好吗?
Deedee, this is a huge misunderstanding, all right?
我们回度假村去，好好谈谈。我不想伤害你。
Let's go back to the resort, talk this over. I do not want to hurt you.
那就别朝我们开枪，混蛋!
Then stop shooting at us, asshole!
别再叫她迪迪了!
And stop calling her Deedee!
——操!-哦，天哪!
- Fuck! - Oh, Jesus!
这东西太可怕了!
This thing is awful!
是啊!
Yeah!
混蛋!他妈的离开!搞什么鬼?
Asshole! Fuckin' leave! What the fuck?
天啊，我真不敢相信你，肖恩!你什么时候变成这样的怪物了?
God, I can't believe you, Sean! When did you turn into such a monster?
我不是怪物!
I am not a monster!
我是个企业家!
I'm an entrepreneur!
我想我没子弹了。
I think I'm out of ammo.
-你确定?-一点也不。
- Are you sure? - Not at all.
嘿。
Hey.
-是的。-我不想这么做。
- Yeah. - I don't wanna do this.
我是个好人，该死!
I'm a good guy, damn it!
大便。
Shit.
你的船死了。
Your boat's dead.
我们都没子弹了。我们回去把这整件事都解决了。
We're both out of ammo. Let's just go back and we can work this whole thing out.
汤姆!
Tom!
走,走!
Go, go!
达西，马上调头。
Darcy, turn this boat around right now.
不。
No.
你是个混蛋，肖恩，但我知道你杀不了我。
You're a piece of shit, Sean, but I know you can't kill me.
你是对的。
You're right.
但我很想杀了这家伙。
But I would love to kill this guy.
你总是把事情搞砸，伙计。这是你的责任。
You just keep messing things up, man. This is on you.
我不想这么做。我是个好人。
I don't wanna do this. I'm a good guy.
不，你不是。
No, you're not.
好吧，你说得对。我不是。
All right, you're right. I'm not.
肖恩!
Sean!
你真可惜!
You were a pity invite!
狗屎!
Shit!
哇!哇!
Whoa! Whoa!
不!他妈的!
No! Fuck!
那是一团散乱的头发吗?
Is that a wad of loose hair?
定制的头发!
Custom-made hair!
下来!
Get down!
哦,弗里克。
Oh, frick.
等一等。
Hold on.
哦,狗屎。
Oh, shit.
天呐
Holy shit.
所以我之前问你我们能不能重新开始
So when I asked you before if we could start over...
我不想重新开始。
I don't wanna start over.
我想继续前进。
I wanna keep going.
汤姆·福勒，你愿意嫁给我吗?
Tom Fowler, will you marry me?
你确定吗?
Are you sure?
你不害怕吗?
You're not scared?
我吓坏了。
I'm terrified.
生活总是混乱的。
Life is always gonna be chaotic.
但我可以肯定的是…我想和你一起经历这一切
But what I know for sure... is that I wanna go through all of it with you.
这真的很简单。
It's simple, really.
只是一个一步的计划。
Just a plan with one step.
仍然符合。
Still fits.
停止。保持安静。
Stop. Be quiet.
狗屎!对不起!对不起!
Shit! Sorry! Sorry!
还剩下一个烟花，我以为它会很有趣，很漂亮，很辛酸，但它绝对不是!
There was one firework left and I thought it would be fun, and beautiful, and poignant, but it was absolutely not!
到这里来。
Come here.
♬坟墓上所有的旧画♬
♪ All the old paintings On the tomb ♪
♬他们在跳沙滩舞，你不知道吗
♪ They do the sand dance, Don't you know ♪
♪如果你走得太快♪
♪ If you move too fast ♪
♪噢噢噢噢♪
♪ Oh-way-oh ♪
♬他们像多米诺骨牌一样倒下
♪ They're falling down Like a domino ♪
♬尼罗河边所有的集市男人♬
♪ All the bazaar men By the Nile ♪
♬他们打赌得到了钱♬
♪ They got the money On a bet ♪
♬金鳄鱼♬
♪ Gold crocodiles ♪
♪噢噢噢噢♪
♪ Oh-way-oh ♪
♬他们咬你的香烟♬
♪ They snap their teeth On your cigarette ♪
♬国外的类型用水烟管说♬
♪ Foreign types With the hookah pipes say ♪
♬噢噢噢噢♬
♪ Way-oh-way-oh ♪
♬走起路来像个埃及人
♪ Walk like an Egyptian ♪
♬金发女服务员拿着他们的托盘♬
♪ The blonde waitresses Take their trays ♪
♬他们旋转，他们穿过地板♬
♪ They spin around And they cross the floor ♪
♬他们有自己的舞步
♪ They've got the moves ♪
♪噢噢噢噢♪
♪ Oh-way-oh ♪
♬所有的学生都讨厌书♬
♪ All the school kids So sick of books ♪
他们喜欢朋克和金属乐队
♪ They like the punk And the metal band ♪
♬我不知道该怎么做♬
♪ I do not know what to do ♪
♬我喝太多了哦，天哪，我生病了♬
♪ I drank so much Oh, my God, I'm sick ♪
♬所有的孩子在市场上说♬
♪ All the kids In the marketplace say ♪
♬噢噢噢噢♬
♪ Way-oh-way-oh ♪
♬走起路来像个埃及人
♪ Walk like an Egyptian ♪
♬我爱上了他的感觉
♪ I'm down For the way he feels ♪
哇!
Whoo!
确保电池正常工作。
Make sure the batteries work.
我很抱歉邀请了两个骗子参加你的婚礼。
I'm so sorry that I invited two con men to your wedding.
我不知道是我喜欢有毒的人，还是有毒的人喜欢我。
And I don't know if I'm attracted to toxic people, or toxic people are attracted to me.